<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<w:document xmlns:wpc="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingCanvas" xmlns:mc="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/markup-compatibility/2006" xmlns:o="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" xmlns:r="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/relationships" xmlns:m="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/math" xmlns:v="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:vml" xmlns:wp14="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingDrawing" xmlns:wp="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/wordprocessingDrawing" xmlns:w10="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:word" xmlns:w="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/wordprocessingml/2006/main" xmlns:w14="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordml" xmlns:w15="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2012/wordml" xmlns:wpg="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingGroup" xmlns:wpi="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingInk" xmlns:wne="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2006/wordml" xmlns:wps="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingShape" xmlns:cx="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/drawing/2014/chartex" xmlns:cx1="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/drawing/2015/9/8/chartex" xmlns:cx2="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/drawing/2015/10/21/chartex" xmlns:cx3="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/drawing/2016/5/9/chartex" xmlns:cx4="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/drawing/2016/5/10/chartex" xmlns:cx5="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/drawing/2016/5/11/chartex" xmlns:cx6="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/drawing/2016/5/12/chartex" xmlns:cx7="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/drawing/2016/5/13/chartex" xmlns:cx8="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/drawing/2016/5/14/chartex" xmlns:aink="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/drawing/2016/ink" xmlns:am3d="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/drawing/2017/model3d" xmlns:w16cex="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2018/wordml/cex" xmlns:w16cid="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2016/wordml/cid" xmlns:w16="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2018/wordml" xmlns:w16sdtdh="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2020/wordml/sdtdatahash" xmlns:w16se="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2015/wordml/symex" mc:Ignorable="w14 w15 wp14">
  <w:body>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">00:05</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Hey, how's it going? Hey. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">00:07</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Good. How are you? </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">00:09</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">I'm good. I. My voice. I've lost my voice a little bit, so I. I apologize if it's not coming out in HD quality. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">00:18</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Oh, no worries. I feel like everyone's like getting sick or whatnot. It's that time of year, so. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">00:25</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Really, really is. Give me one second. Let me just. My headphones. How are you? How's your day? </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">00:30</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">I'm good, I'm good. I'm in Sage currently. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">00:34</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Nice. So you're. You're the MBA program, is it? </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">00:39</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Yeah, yeah, exactly. So I can kind of like give an instruction myself and I could tell you a little bit about like Gorgeous Ventures and then would love to hear about you. I know that you're an MBA from Johnson as well. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">00:51</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">That's right. Yep. Guilty as charged. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">00:55</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Yeah, I. So yeah, I'm a second year mba. Before business school, I was working at Carney, which is just a management consulting firm and their private equity and M and A practice. And then I'm here as a Park fellow. I've just like absolutely loved Johnson so far and have been focusing more on entrepreneurship, venture capital. I'm in Elab as well, like building a business currently and. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">01:23</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Oh, you're building. You're building as well. Cool. What are you building? </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">01:26</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Yeah, I'm building right now like a sample box of period products for women. So they could like try all different types of these, like smaller brands versus like the ones that are like Procter. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">01:39</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">And Gamble owned and that is so cool. Wait, can you. When you launch that, can you send it to me? I have so many friends that would like, so appreciate that. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">01:48</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Yeah, absolutely. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">01:49</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">They're all. I know, I know a lot of my friends are looking to not just divest, but just generally speaking, support smaller brands or stuff that is a little bit more aligned with their values. Yeah, that would be awesome. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">02:02</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Yeah, I would love that. That'd be awesome. And then, yeah, Gorgeous Ventures. I don't know. Have you heard of the. It's like it's smaller. They just started it last year. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">02:15</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">I. I believe I spoke to your colleague. I forget where her name is. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">02:20</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Megan. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">02:22</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Megan, that's right. Sort of, sort of slightly harder pronounced last name. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">02:27</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Yeah, yeah. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">02:29</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Okay. We don't try. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">02:30</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">We don't try. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">02:31</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Yeah, well, I have. I have a tough to pronounce first name, so, you know, I totally. I get that life. No, that makes. That makes sense. No, I had. I had a wonderful conversation with Megan. So to give you that context and obviously you'll. You'll. Hear from her as well. You know, essentially had a wonderful conversation with her, gave her a sense of what we're doing without putting words in her mouth. It seemed she was very sort of interested in the premise and certainly in sort of the substance of what we're doing. I think the last discussion was timing doesn't feel right. We were still, I would say, seeking out product market fit in many ways. I'd say right now we're much further along in that process. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">03:10</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">In fact, I would say more so were just trying to refine our, go to market and really like lock in on, okay, we've almost built this great product. What is the way in which we monetize it? So to give you my introduction, my context, you know, started my career international student, came to the US for school, you know, very much had the experience of coming from a fair amount of privilege, but also being completely unaccustomed to what hiring was like in the U.S. and what, you know, anything from like basic interview etiquette to, you know, you name it. And very much struggled at the outset of my life with that. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">03:51</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Over time, however, moved to Singapore, got into college admissions coaching and then eventually became sort of a resume doctor myself in large part, lots of career coaching in large part because of that strength and narrative design. And that's sort of our core philosophy as a company is that to really assess someone, to really get to know someone, you have to understand their story. And so what our product does is a process of guided self reflection through conversation with our AI. It's a way for you to, for instance, you're doing what I'm sure is a bang up job with Gorgeous Ventures. So actually being able to at the end of the week, after you've done a project or made some achievement, just jump on, spend 10 minutes, log an experience with Careerspan. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">04:36</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">And what we're finding is that our users are very excited, very happy to being able to store stuff at that sort of higher fidelity in that higher fidelity way. Stow it away and then also leverage it continuously or repeatedly for. To help them get jobs. Yeah, yeah. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">04:56</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">So it's like, so it's more of that like continuous update versus like I haven't updated my resume in like three years. I'm so overwhelmed. Like, where do I begin? It's trying to get people to like start that process like, and do it continuously. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">05:18</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Precisely, precisely. We're called Career Span because we feel like folks need to treat their careers more like preventative health and more of a sort of holistic way. Right. As opposed to right now. You know, I can say with extreme confidence or my vantage point that most of us, we work on our careers at the exact wrong times. Right. We will like, you know, try to build a network when we should have one warmed up, ready to go. Right. Or we will, to your point, sit down and write a resume once we've already emotionally checked out from the place and don't want to talk about it. Right. So there's a variety of these. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">05:55</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">I think that is the thing that I'm proudest of is as a company we are trying to solve frankly much harder problems than just the technical problems of gang and AI to behave, which is in itself quite significant. But it's also how do we create a coaching experience or a facilitation experience that ends up with folks being better job seekers? Yeah, the last sort of piece of the puzzle is actually okay, well this is all well and good. How do you make money? Which by the way, for some context into our numbers, we have over 1,000 hours of coaching recorded across 3,000 signups and about a third of those users have recorded one or multiple conversations with our AI. So it's a pretty good number just right off the bat. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">06:43</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">And that's before you even consider that this is not just swiping here and There, this is 10 to 20 minutes of concerted self reflection on the part of users. So I think we really cracked that part of the UX. We have a D30 retention number of about 20% and then that sort of halves going down but stabilizes at about 5, 6% at the six month mark, which again is basically twice as good. It's very much in line with sort of best of class usage for consumer. And in terms of monetization, what we're thinking right now is effectively can we just continue to drive people into career span? </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">07:26</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Our exit strategy is almost to keep growing our user base because there are some companies coming out of the UK that are doing quite well and we actually suspect that we will get, we're like a great target for acquisition essentially. So that's what we're effectively hoping to do is just stay an appealing target for as long as we can. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">07:50</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">So these are these UK companies like your, you would be like their user base for breaking into the US market. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">07:56</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Effectively or someone in the US market that wants something that's spun up. I mean the companies in question are Dex and Jack and Jill and both Very well funded, you know, a 16Z speed run kind of tier stuff. We have better tech than them, frankly. I think their huge advantage is that their founders came into HR with a lot of credibility and with a lot of sort of established experience in recruiting. I think thus far we've tried to play that game and frankly, not had a lot of success. So we're, you know, now thinking, let's go back to our roots. You know, we're not actually even trying to raise money necessarily. We're just trying to say, hey, can we bring more and more users in? And we actually have some really great relationships with communities. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">08:43</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">And so part of the other reason I wanted to chat was because I'm hoping to make more inroads into Cornell and actually have Cornell's alumni association. So Emory, their alumni association is going to distribute us to their entire alumni base. Tens of thousands of folks. Yeah. We're effectively able to offer the, literally the best product in the market of its type for free for, you know, because we have developed it well enough to build that network effect. Yeah. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">09:13</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Have you thought about, like, speaking with the cmc, like, the career services of, like. I know, like, for example, when we first started Johnson, like, we got an email that we needed update our resumes, and, like, they wanted us to put it into that, like, AI resume tool. And, like, they had it as a requirement, which, like, I feel like Johnson students could be, like, a very interesting case because, like, you're doing so much in these two years. It's so different. And, like, people are career pivoting that, like, having these students do it would be, like. I think it would be, like, super. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">09:49</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Helpful for people, for sure. I mean, hey, frankly, I probably know more about application tech than any human alive. Like, I don't even mean that in a boastful way. It's actually embarrassing to spend so much time thinking about resume builders of all things. But I can say with pretty complete confidence that, like, vmox sucks. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">10:10</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Yeah. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">10:10</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Oh, yeah. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">10:11</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">I, like, literally put it into vmock and then I was like, I did it. I'm like, my resume sucks now, and I, like, completely redo that everything again. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">10:17</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Yeah, yeah, it sucks. It's just better formatted. Right. VMock is completely useless. And I, I. You would be offended if I told you how much they pay for vmock. You know, we're actually up for consideration for the cmc. If you've got any good ideas around how I can maybe engage with more students. You know, it's been a while Since I've been connected to the Johnson community. But I would love to at the very least get a survey out to students to kind of get their honest opinion on vmod. Because I can say confidently, having been through the goddamn program that, you know, CMC is overloaded. They can't sit down and help us think through all of the cool shit we've done. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">10:55</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Oh, they don't do like anything. Yeah, it's like all students. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">10:59</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Yeah. No, but imagine how much better would be at CMC if you had, for instance, gotten career span over the summer. You'd used it to record a couple of experiences about yourself. CMC doesn't just get your resume, they get. Actually, do you mind if I just show you? </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">11:13</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Yeah, of course. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">11:16</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Like a proud dad. So, you know, this is just a sample company so it doesn't have all of the details. It's not a fully pop. Actually give me one second. I'm going to get you a populated account while I just show you the basics because I think it really illustrates the point. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">11:35</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Yeah. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">11:35</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Quick. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">11:36</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Yeah, I'm happy to like, while you're pulling it up, like I'm happy to even just like share if you have a survey you want me to share in like our cross chat like WhatsApp group. That's between like the first and second years. People post surveys like that would be. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">11:50</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">That would be awesome. And I'm happy to. I'll think of some way I can sort of give back to the Johnson community as well. I don't know if you, do you ever do consulting at all? Were you ever on the consulting path? </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">12:02</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">I did consulting before and I'm helping Carney like recruit while being here, so. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">12:07</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Oh, cool. The reason I ask. Well, the reason I ask is because like I, the last sort of major touch point I had with Johnson was I put this together and I know folks have been using it over the last few years. So yeah, this in case you've come across. It was me. Oh, also, I'm sorry, have I just been video off this whole freaking time? </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">12:31</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">It, it went off. But I didn't know it was your connection. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">12:34</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">So sorry about that. Yeah. Okay, cool. Here we are. Here, here I am. Yeah. Sorry. Not just trying to be strange. So, you know, I, I, I'll send that. I mean I'm happy to have that be put back in circulation as well because it is genuinely like a super useful thing that I put together. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">12:52</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Yeah. Also like, I think your story of like being like coming from like as an international student as well could like really resonate because just like in terms of what's happening at the university level like with the H1B1 visas and a lot of our like our class is less international than the second, the first years and I think they're like 6% even more international than us. And there's a lot of like people are very anxious, very stressed about recruiting because the job market sucks and. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">13:22</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">This visa stuff that's is there is this directly top of mind for any of your candidates? Because I mean again like why is this switching to like my weird angle camera? Sorry, one second. This is just like uncomfortable be looking at my profile. I. If it's top of mind for any of your teachers or classmates or whomever. I mean I'm happy to put myself forward as someone that can contribute an informed opinion because not only do I literally work with recruiters and founders and hiring managers have pretty tapped into that sort of side of the market as you said, have that sort of experience of both sides of trying to make it as an international and then also having the perspective. So yeah, I'm happy to sort of speak, talk. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">14:08</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">I candidly have like taken on probably maybe like half a dozen Johnson internationals over the years just like sort of, you know, they've done good work for us. So yeah, I'm pretty, I'm pretty sort of happy to put my money out there as far as the community is concerned. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">14:27</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Yeah. Or even just like these could be people like you're like growing your user base. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">14:32</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Totally. Yeah. I mean, hey, we, we. Part of the reason why, you know, I spent so much time just even talking about monetization is because this would be, this is a great product. I have the same sort of consumer numbers that anyone else would monetize with. It's just we don't feel comfortable asking job seekers to pay. It just doesn't feel right. It also just doesn't feel like a strong long term business strategy. I think job seekers are the valuable resource because companies we have evidence are willing to pay 20 to 60 grand for the right person. And so you know, I think it's from our perspective it's more about sort of putting that power back into folks. But I'll just sort of illustrate very quickly the kind of stuff that we can do. You know this account has two stories. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">15:17</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">So you'll see, you know, this person was just giving responses. You know, you'll see here like these responses are you know, not super robust. They're Kind of more test responses, but it's able to extract, like, pretty strong stuff out of just a conversation with the AI, you're able to get, based off of these deeper understandings of who you are. Because, remember, resume is actually a very thin slice of who you are. Right. In terms of salient information, and especially the interrelationship between the things that you do here, we absorb that in its entirety. So the actual type of analysis we're able to do is much better. We can actually tell you what the critical gaps in your story are, which ones you need to be ready to talk about. You can fill that gap by telling a story. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">16:09</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">You can say, okay, this job, I have something that exhibits analytical thinking. Let me fill that out. And in fact, if that story covers multiple things, multiple of these will sort of light up. And so it'll actually give you a very programmatic way of figuring out, are you a good fit for this job? And so you can just dump in a job description and it'll do all of this for you. And it will actually, also, just to show you very quickly, the narrative part, it will actually develop a narrative for you. It'll tell you how to position yourself, which aspects of yourself to emphasize, what your strengths coming into this are. It gets incrementally updated every time you add a story. It maps you onto what we reckon the average applicant relative to the average applicant would be. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">16:57</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">So this candidate, as a financial analyst, coming from a teacher background, very unique, right? </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">17:04</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Yeah. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">17:04</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">You can see logically that is not the only factor. Right. Because they actually don't have a lot of these. These other variables that we would be looking for. If I were to run another job that was, you know, maybe more relevant. I think there's a project manager job here somewhere. You can see that there is. Again, intuitively, we know that the work of a teacher, which is more project management, is more aligned with the manager, which is also. So you can see that there's an internal consistency as well, because we've actually built it out to be that way. The final piece of it is companies paying us to have this ready to apply button for sourced by careerspan companies where we can quick check against our database and essentially, you know, no more waiting weeks for candidates. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">17:51</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Like, within an hour, I'll give you a list of folks that you can reach out to. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">17:55</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Okay. Yeah. So if you. So you're not charging. This is awesome, by the way. Like, thanks for. Thanks for showing me this. This is really cool. So if you were just for understanding of the business, like, you're not charging people to use it. So are you like, are you making revenue in any way or like, is it that link to the businesses or to like the resumes to apply? </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">18:18</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">So now interestingly our thinking is, and this, a lot of this is just evolving as well, right? So again, you know, maybe it's a sign of a bad founder to be this candid, but hey, I'm going to roll the dice, see what works here. We see where we land. I think where we have the strongest motivation and clearest value prop is as a really great product for job seekers, both active and passive. And so effectively we're trying to tell ourselves and I think for most of the year we're putting a lot of pressure ourselves of like, we've got to hit certain revenue numbers to like BVC fundable. And now what we're telling ourselves is we have a great product, it retains the shit out of people. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">18:58</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">You know, we have folks a year later that are organically locking onto, you know, 6 to 8% of folks within a year will log back into Career span and update a story. I mean that's incredible, right? So given that dynamic that exists, we're thinking can we just do things that drive more people to Career span? And I think that's a lengthy way of saying we are charging a minuscule amount to let folks use CareerSpan as an ATS or to run stuff against Careerspan. It's not really driving like more than let's say $1,000 a month worth of non recurring revenue. But what is promising is that we're seeing it sort of like tick up and we're effectively thinking, okay, can we just having those jobs on Careerspan is drawing people in. So can we just do that for a little bit? </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">19:48</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Build this flywheel, ideally get into a couple of communities like Johnson, my co founder is talking about HBS next week. So can we get into a couple of these communities and really start to just have folks embed on the platform? Because in that regard we're basically just a very low cost, high retention network that we're building that we can layer on top of. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">20:12</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Yeah, totally. So it's like, because it's like you mentioned like you have better tech. Are these the Jack and Jill and the Dex platforms are like more funded? </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">20:22</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">They have, they're more fun. I, my, yeah, so the interpretation that I have and again obviously it's coming from a biased source, but you can look at the underlying facts yourself. Both founded by ex recruiters, both have a lot of industry connections. Win this. Sorry, my cat is sitting on my keyboard now. Sorry, buddy, your camera's off again, but no worries. Sorry about that. Yeah, well, actually you missed. You missed a good one because it's. It's this guy. Oh yeah, there you go. You see him? So I'll actually just address you here and this is easier instead of this game, you know, effectively Jack and Jill started by ex recruiters. Are you familiar with Bordeaux Bord's been going kind of viral on parts of like investor startup Twitter. They're basically. You just like call it. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">21:11</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">It has a conversation with you and then it connects you to other people. Pretty cool concept. They are effectively boardy, which has lots of overlaps with us. Right. Their approach is more a. What they have essentially done is turned a onboarding process into a boardy style conversation, which is great and it does do a lot as far as helping you know more about the candidate and their motivations. The reason their model is intrinsically limited is because they are not then trying to turn that into a resume killer. Right. Because ultimately, I think you and I will agree continuing to hire people off of resumes is being very analog in a world that isn't just digital. It's fucking quantum. Right? Yeah, it's just very backwards. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">21:59</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">I think the appropriate data structure for a modern resume is a data structure that is easily indexable, easily searchable, carries nuanced information, not just keywords, and is actually a thing that you develop on an ongoing basis in a very human centric way. Right. Talk about vision. That is what we deserve as candidates. Neither of those companies is positioned to do that. We have the underlying tech to do that, which is why our approach is more time intensive. But the, but the grade of data that you get is an order of magnitude better because we are asking you to do deep dives into a particular experience. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">22:43</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Yeah, no, that's. That's fantastic. It's awesome. I'm. I think it makes a lot of sense. And if you, are you working on this like full time, if you're not going to. Okay. Because you've got enough funding to hold you over for now. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">22:57</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Yeah, we're essentially slimming down the team. We have enough, we expect enough money to like cover the 25, 30 grand a month burn. So we're essentially trying to just stabilize and grow value and essentially thinking like, hey, why dilute further? Right. We have something great. We just need to, you know, keep things running to keep it afloat. That being said, I do. I did also want to have this conversation. I know it's like again, ostensibly a little strange for me to emphasize how little we're trying to raise. One of the reasons why in addition to the fact this is Cornell and obviously want to build these relationships with the long term, is that we have an outside chance of monetizing through VCs by essentially offering access to career span as a VC perk. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">23:45</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">And so I was wondering, I know you guys have a small but mighty portfolio or at least trying to grow it. Is that just a perk that you guys would be willing to offer? I mean, I don't know if that's something that you've considered as part of what you do, but it would be a great way to support a Johnson founder. It would be a, you know, easy way for you to literally audit our tech in case there's any chance of sort of us being an investment opportunity. And I mean hopefully you can tell by the caliber of analysis I showed you that it's substantive. Right. Yeah. It's at least going to give you stuff that will be of value even if it doesn't turn up a, a guaranteed candidate for your folks. So I wanted to put that out there as well. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">24:28</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">And I'm happy to package all of this in a follow up email. Get that to you. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">24:31</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Yeah, no, I think what's like one thing to just note is like so our class fund is technically separate than like the class above us is fund. So like we work together but like we're separate LLC and we're interesting. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">24:46</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Okay. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">24:47</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">So I, I think that like I'm more than happy to have like a conversation with Megan because they've deployed their capital yet like we have it, we're in the fundraising, we're doing our first close and then we're going to be deploying capital so we don't have like a robust. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">25:03</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Right, right. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">25:04</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Portfolio. I think that like probably asking like Megan and their team on that would be better. But I am happy to help is like if you want me to facilitate anything with putting that survey in. If you want to have a conversation with. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">25:22</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Yeah. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">25:22</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">And like if you want to have a conversation with. It's like all the presidents of the clubs, like the professional clubs meet together like once a week. And so like I'm in high tech club on the board of that and then like we, they. So if you want it to be like a conversation that they have or like, or make a conversation with them, I connect, can connect you with like I forget It's. Her name's Brianna. She's like a close friend of mine, but she kind of like oversees all of the professional that would be person to chat with. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">25:57</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">That would be spectacular. Yeah, an intro to Brianna and I'll generate a blurb for you. An intro to Brianna would be absolutely stellar because yeah, I do think that, you know, there's a. There's a huge extent to which I know Michael has tried to get HDC to like take a look at career span or sort of check out career span here and there. I think it's just much more powerful when it comes pushed from like the student leaders as opposed to cmc, which like I love Michael but like, you know, we like CMC is not taken super seriously by students. Like let's just call it what it is. I think it's much more powerful coming from folks that actually know that can like kind of speak to the tech. So I'll say this. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">26:38</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">The other thing that is also really powerful with careerspan is we can actually distribute jobs through careerspan. So if you give me a jd, we can set it up such that only Cornell folks are only folks from your professional club and that too only folks that are qualified get surfaced. So it's also just a one size fits all mechanism for you to distribute jobs to people. Right. So I know I've thrown a lot at you. Very quickly, before we leave, two things. One, I will package everything up and sort of get to you and I'll get the blurbs and all of it. I actually have a pretty cool automation system to do all of this for me. So I feel nowadays very comfortable committing to detailed follow up. The other thing that I will say is how can I be helpful to you personally? </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">27:26</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Like what are you hoping to do after Johnson? What are you hoping. Is there something you're hoping to build with your brand or particular types of connections? Like how can I. Yeah, how can I help, Zoe? </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">27:36</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Well, I appreciate that. I would say like I'm kind of more in like the femtech, like femcare space. So I don't know if you happen to know anyone. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">27:47</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Yes, you know who you should talk to. Give me one second. Do you have a second? Can I look through my LinkedIn for you real quick? </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">27:54</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Yeah, yeah, I probably. I have one. Another one other call, but maybe let's do like two more minutes or so. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">27:59</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Yeah, yeah, give me two seconds. There's one name in particular and I can try to get you an intro to her, but I know actually a couple of Folks. So there's Maddie Holburn who is an absolute powerhouse at Daring Ventures and I know she is quite invest and she's like great LinkedIn follow. Just very talented woman. I can try to do a intro to you. She didn't respond to my last message, so I want to be candid about that. But you know, my last message was also about like following up with her about shit. She gets a lot of messages about. Just one second. Yeah, if you have to jump, by all means. But there's a few folks that I can run through for you that are either founders. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">28:55</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Can I clarify, Are you looking to work as an operator in femtech once you graduate or found a femtech company once you graduate? </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">29:02</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">So it's looking to like, hopefully take what I'm working in Elab, but I am like committed back to Carney. Like I signed my offer so I'm not like, just really like looking. I mean I don't need to return back to them, but so it's less like, you know, what I would be interested in like operating too and like having those conversations. So it's kind of anything in that space really. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">29:27</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Let me, let me. Because there's some folks that if it's the person, I remember correctly, she was actually doing something. There's one person I know that's actually building in the PCOS space that's trying to build around sort of like a awareness tool that has a doctor based gtm. I'll put together some names and get you some folks. I really appreciate your time and you support us, so I'd love to get you back and yeah, looking forward to staying in touch. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">29:53</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Zoe Weber</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Of course. Amazing. Well, it's really nice to meet you. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:p>
      <w:r>
        <w:rPr>
          <w:b/>
          <w:bCs/>
        </w:rPr>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">29:55</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">Vrijen Attawar</w:t>
      </w:r>
      <w:r>
        <w:br/>
        <w:t xml:space="preserve">All right, catch you soon. Take care. Bye. Hello. Hi. How are you? Yeah, yeah, I'm sorry, the house is a lot dirtier this week. I've just been working. I really appreciate it. They're, they're doing okay. I got amazing. That did the trick. </w:t>
      </w:r>
    </w:p>
    <w:sectPr>
      <w:headerReference w:type="default" r:id="rId6"/>
      <w:pgSz w:w="11906" w:h="16838" w:orient="portrait"/>
      <w:pgMar w:top="1in" w:right="1in" w:bottom="1in" w:left="1in" w:header="708" w:footer="708" w:gutter="0"/>
      <w:pgNumType/>
      <w:docGrid w:linePitch="360"/>
    </w:sectPr>
  </w:body>
</w:document>
