{"entities": [{"name": "V", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder of Careerspan, owns university sales motion, works on acquisition sprints and B2B sales"}, {"name": "Logan", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Collaborator who proposed three-part execution system, works on acquisition sprints and marketing"}, {"name": "Ilya", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Collaborator working on B2B sales motion and marketing execution"}, {"name": "Irene", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Has visited approximately 10 campuses, warm entry point for higher-ed"}, {"name": "Daniel", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Has a job-fair company, potential partnership path"}, {"name": "Julie", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Connection for Kellogg business school"}, {"name": "Kellogg", "type": "ORG", "context": "Business school, potential university partner via Julie"}, {"name": "Wharton", "type": "ORG", "context": "Business school with chief of staff as warm entry point"}, {"name": "Three-part execution system", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Logan's proposed framework: acquisition sprints, B2B sales motion, marketing campaigns"}, {"name": "Acquisition targeting sprints", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "30-minute focused sessions on Tuesdays/Thursdays to blitz outreach by category"}, {"name": "B2B sales motion", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Demos and follow-ups with founders and B2B buyers, inbound and outbound"}, {"name": "Alumni offices as wedge", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "GTM angle: universities want alumni data for donations, existing alumni-tech is inadequate"}, {"name": "Job fairs as integration", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "High-leverage GTM angle where students see many employers at once"}, {"name": "University sales", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Long-cycle but highly leveraged motion, ~10-15% of V's time"}], "relationships": [{"from": "V", "to": "Logan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Collaborate on acquisition/targeting sprints"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Ilya", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Collaborate on B2B sales motion"}, {"from": "Logan", "to": "Ilya", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Collaborate on marketing and campaigns"}, {"from": "Logan", "to": "Three-part execution system", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Logan proposed this execution framework for the next few months"}, {"from": "V", "to": "University sales", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "V keeps ownership, treating as 10-15% of his time"}, {"from": "Julie", "to": "Kellogg", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Julie is the connection path to Kellogg"}, {"from": "Daniel", "to": "Job fairs as integration", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Daniel has a job-fair company relevant to this GTM angle"}, {"from": "Irene", "to": "University sales", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Irene has visited ~10 campuses, warm entry point"}, {"from": "Three-part execution system", "to": "Acquisition targeting sprints", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "First part of the execution system"}, {"from": "Three-part execution system", "to": "B2B sales motion", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Second part of the execution system"}]}