{"entities": [{"name": "Anthony", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Subject of intelligence gathering; former Visit Days employee, potential Careerspan user, father, seeking senior IC product role"}, {"name": "Daniel Shalinsky", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Potential warm intro connection to Anthony"}, {"name": "Visit Days", "type": "ORG", "context": "Company where Anthony previously worked; outcome unclear (acquired, shut down, or ongoing)"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company; Anthony abandoned it previously due to unspecified friction"}, {"name": "NACAC", "type": "ORG", "context": "National Association for College Admission Counseling; conference archives as intel source"}, {"name": "NACE", "type": "ORG", "context": "National Association of Colleges and Employers; resources for higher ed industry intel"}, {"name": "Education Dive", "type": "ORG", "context": "Publication covering higher ed industry"}, {"name": "EdSurge", "type": "ORG", "context": "Publication covering higher ed/edtech"}, {"name": "Inside Higher Ed", "type": "ORG", "context": "Publication with relevant mentions"}, {"name": "Berkshires", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Anthony's location; potential community involvement"}, {"name": "Senior IC Product", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Anthony's stated ideal next role type"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Anthony", "to": "Visit Days", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Former employee; left recently, timing possibly related to fatherhood"}, {"from": "Anthony", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Previously abandoned the platform; specific friction points unknown"}, {"from": "Anthony", "to": "Daniel Shalinsky", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Relationship unclear; potential warm intro pathway"}, {"from": "Anthony", "to": "Berkshires", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Current location; community involvement unknown"}, {"from": "Visit Days", "to": "NACAC", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Higher ed industry connection"}, {"from": "Visit Days", "to": "NACE", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Higher ed industry connection"}]}