{"entities": [{"name": "Vrijen", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder of Careerspan, presenting university pipeline results and business model options"}, {"name": "Kamina", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Collaborator who challenges Vrijen's assumptions and encourages charging institutions"}, {"name": "Felix", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact at Rice University involved in Careerspan conversations"}, {"name": "Jim Pike", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact at Rice University involved in Careerspan conversations"}, {"name": "Diane", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Connection maintaining ties between Vrijen and Columbia"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "Vrijen's company offering career development tools to students and institutions"}, {"name": "UMass Amherst", "type": "ORG", "context": "University with strong proof results from undergrad business cohort (~92% strengthened experiences)"}, {"name": "Rice", "type": "ORG", "context": "University with ongoing interest in Careerspan"}, {"name": "Columbia", "type": "ORG", "context": "University with existing ties via Diane"}, {"name": "Cornell Johnson", "type": "ORG", "context": "MBA program considering Careerspan adoption two years after initial outreach"}, {"name": "University of Mount Saint Vincent", "type": "ORG", "context": "Resource-constrained institution mentioned as pricing example"}, {"name": "VMock", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Competitor tool that Careerspan could replace at schools"}, {"name": "University pipeline", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Strategy for proving value and re-engaging schools with Careerspan"}, {"name": "Institutional inertia", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Frustration with slow, cautious career center gatekeepers despite student demand"}, {"name": "Free shelfware", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Risk Kamina warns against when giving tools away at no cost"}, {"name": "Two pricing models", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "(a) Direct to schools at $10-15k or (b) employer-funded with near-cost school license"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Kamina", "to": "Vrijen", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Challenges assumptions and encourages charging institutions"}, {"from": "Felix", "to": "Rice", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Involved in Careerspan conversations at Rice"}, {"from": "Jim Pike", "to": "Rice", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Involved in Careerspan conversations at Rice"}, {"from": "Diane", "to": "Columbia", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Maintains ties between Vrijen and Columbia"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "UMass Amherst", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Strong proof results from undergrad business cohort"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "VMock", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Positioned as potential replacement at $10-15k price point"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Cornell Johnson", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "MBA program reconsidering adoption after two-year gap"}, {"from": "Kamina", "to": "Free shelfware", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Warns against giving tools away free to avoid shelfware problem"}, {"from": "Kamina", "to": "Institutional inertia", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Vents about schools balking at $20 while charging $100k+ tuition"}]}