{"entities": [{"name": "Vrijen", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder of Careerspan, coordinating partnership activities and technical validation"}, {"name": "Oscar", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Collaborator from Marvin, handles Getro admin, WhatsApp announcements, and partnership coordination"}, {"name": "J", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact who will help set up Careerspan on LinkedIn"}, {"name": "Ulrich", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact who will help launch Careerspan's LinkedIn presence for Marvin"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company, being integrated with Marvin's ecosystem"}, {"name": "Marvin", "type": "ORG", "context": "Partner organization with founders, newsletter, and LinkedIn presence"}, {"name": "Getro", "type": "ORG", "context": "Platform providing job exports; contract implications to be revisited Q3 2026"}, {"name": "Net1", "type": "ORG", "context": "Network within Getro where Vrijen was added as admin"}, {"name": "LinkedIn", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Platform for Careerspan presence and rotating mentions"}, {"name": "WhatsApp", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Channel for partnership announcement"}, {"name": "Scraping pipeline", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Technical solution to replicate Getro functionality before Q3 2026"}, {"name": "LOI", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Letter of Intent stage gating several coordination tasks"}, {"name": "Q3 2026", "type": "EVENT", "context": "Future milestone for revisiting partnership and Getro contract implications"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Oscar", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Coordinating partnership launch, announcements, and ongoing tracking"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "J", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Setting up Careerspan on LinkedIn post-LOI"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Ulrich", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Launching Careerspan's LinkedIn presence for Marvin"}, {"from": "Oscar", "to": "Ulrich", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Oscar to ping Ulrich once launch is ready"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Marvin", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Partnership with rotating newsletter/LinkedIn mentions and founder access"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Getro", "type": "USES", "context": "Using Getro for job exports; exploring scraping alternative"}, {"from": "Scraping pipeline", "to": "Getro", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Pipeline intended to replicate Getro's functionality"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Founder providing assets, language, and strategic direction"}]}