{"entities": [{"name": "Vrijen", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Main strategist planning community partnerships and event distribution"}, {"name": "Tejas", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Runs the New Jersey chapter of AI Collective, close friend of Vrijen"}, {"name": "Ben Lang", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Speaker giving talks, collaborating on events, not yet ready for full course commitment"}, {"name": "Tiffany", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Participant suggesting course idea as next step after talk repetitions"}, {"name": "AI Collective", "type": "ORG", "context": "Major community with 80-90k people, potential distribution partner for events"}, {"name": "Next Play", "type": "ORG", "context": "Community partner for recurring events, collaboration to be locked down"}, {"name": "South Park Commons", "type": "ORG", "context": "Additional optional community for event inventory"}, {"name": "AI Circle", "type": "ORG", "context": "Additional optional community for event inventory"}, {"name": "Zo", "type": "ORG", "context": "Product/company that Tejas is enthusiastic about"}, {"name": "Staged approach", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Strategy to run talks first, then revisit course idea once more data and cycles available"}, {"name": "Q1 event inventory", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Planning framework targeting an event every 3-4 weeks using partner communities"}, {"name": "Year-end objectives", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Goals to lock down Ben Lang and Tejas/AI Collective as recurring partners"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Tejas", "to": "AI Collective", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Runs the New Jersey chapter"}, {"from": "Tejas", "to": "Vrijen", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Described as close friend"}, {"from": "Tejas", "to": "Ben Lang", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Impressed by Ben, potential intro call planned"}, {"from": "Tejas", "to": "Zo", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Enthusiastic about Zo"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Ben Lang", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Coordinating talks and Next Play collaboration"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Tiffany", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Strategic planning discussions"}, {"from": "Ben Lang", "to": "Next Play", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Collaboration to be locked down post-Thursday"}, {"from": "Tiffany", "to": "Staged approach", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Advocated for staged approach after raising course idea"}, {"from": "Ben Lang", "to": "Staged approach", "type": "USES", "context": "Agreed to keep running talks before committing to course"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Q1 event inventory", "type": "USES", "context": "Sketched event inventory using Next Play and AI Collective"}, {"from": "AI Collective", "to": "Next Play", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Both serve as core event inventory for Q1 planning"}]}