{"entities": [{"name": "Vrijen", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder of Careerspan, committing to outreach and follow-up tasks"}, {"name": "Kamina", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Collaborator with relationships at national programs, exploring funding and acquisition opportunities"}, {"name": "Felix", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact at Rice university"}, {"name": "Jim Pike", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact at Rice university"}, {"name": "Logan", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Advisor Vrijen will consult about ASA acquisition approach"}, {"name": "Jane", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact at ASA that Kamina may approach about acquisition"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "Vrijen's company, seeking school partnerships and potential acquisition"}, {"name": "Rice", "type": "ORG", "context": "University partner/prospect requiring follow-up"}, {"name": "Cornell Johnson", "type": "ORG", "context": "Business school partner/prospect requiring follow-up"}, {"name": "UMass", "type": "ORG", "context": "University with results to be shared as proof metrics"}, {"name": "ASA", "type": "ORG", "context": "Organization with potential acquisition interest"}, {"name": "Strada", "type": "ORG", "context": "Funding organization with potential interest in Careerspan, especially for HBCU support"}, {"name": "HBCUs", "type": "ORG", "context": "Historically Black Colleges and Universities, focus area for Strada funding"}, {"name": "Per Scholas", "type": "ORG", "context": "National program where Kamina has relationships for seeding pilots"}, {"name": "COOP", "type": "ORG", "context": "National program where Kamina has relationships for seeding pilots"}, {"name": "Metrics pack", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Proof materials Vrijen will provide to arm Kamina for funding conversations"}, {"name": "Division of labor", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Framework for splitting commitments between Vrijen and Kamina"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Kamina", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Collaborative partnership on Careerspan outreach and acquisition strategy"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Founder leading outreach and metrics efforts"}, {"from": "Felix", "to": "Rice", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Contact at Rice for follow-up"}, {"from": "Jim Pike", "to": "Rice", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Contact at Rice for follow-up"}, {"from": "Jane", "to": "ASA", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Kamina's contact for potential acquisition conversation"}, {"from": "Kamina", "to": "Per Scholas", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Has relationships to seed pilots or acquisition interest"}, {"from": "Kamina", "to": "COOP", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Has relationships to seed pilots or acquisition interest"}, {"from": "Kamina", "to": "Strada", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Will reach out for funding or acquisition fit"}, {"from": "Kamina", "to": "ASA", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Will explore acquisition through Jane"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Logan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Will consult on whether Kamina should approach Jane at ASA"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "UMass", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "UMass results serve as proof metrics for Careerspan"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Rice", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "School partner/prospect for email outreach"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Cornell Johnson", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "School partner/prospect for follow-up"}, {"from": "Strada", "to": "HBCUs", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Strada funding particularly relevant for HBCU support"}]}