{"entities": [{"name": "Tiffany", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Participant on call with Vrijen, joining from Puerto Rico, mentioned being under the weather"}, {"name": "Vrijen", "type": "PERSON", "context": "The user (V), discussing business momentum and networking opportunities for Zo"}, {"name": "Ben Lang", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Associated with Next Play community, received event options from Vrijen, expressed preference for virtual events"}, {"name": "Ben", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Made Tiffany sick, mentioned in personal context at start of call"}, {"name": "Tejas", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Close friend of Vrijen, recently became New Jersey head of AI Collective"}, {"name": "Next Play", "type": "ORG", "context": "Paid community of 1,000+ members at ~$12/month, considered high-signal, doesn't run many events"}, {"name": "Friends of Next Play", "type": "ORG", "context": "Exclusive space that Ben Lang keeps relatively exclusive, potential channel for experiments"}, {"name": "AI Collective", "type": "ORG", "context": "Organization where Tejas is New Jersey head, eager to bring Zo into the community"}, {"name": "Zo", "type": "ORG", "context": "Product/company being discussed for networking use cases and community events"}, {"name": "RO", "type": "ORG", "context": "Company that has shown eagerness to sponsor events"}, {"name": "Oracle", "type": "ORG", "context": "Company that has shown eagerness to sponsor events"}, {"name": "Acquisition", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Potential acquisition discussions contributing to positive year-end momentum"}, {"name": "Sales momentum", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Solid sales progress mentioned as part of year-end positive trajectory"}, {"name": "Networking use case", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Broader use case for Zo that Vrijen wanted to think through with Tiffany"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Tiffany", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Having strategic call to discuss Zo opportunities"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Ben Lang", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Sent five or six event options, exploring Next Play community partnership"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Tejas", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Described as close friend"}, {"from": "Ben Lang", "to": "Next Play", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Manages or leads the Next Play community"}, {"from": "Ben Lang", "to": "Friends of Next Play", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Keeps the exclusive space relatively controlled"}, {"from": "Tejas", "to": "AI Collective", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Recently became New Jersey head"}, {"from": "Tejas", "to": "Zo", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Eager to bring Zo into AI Collective community"}, {"from": "RO", "to": "Zo", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Eager to sponsor Zo events"}, {"from": "Oracle", "to": "Zo", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Eager to sponsor Zo events"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Networking use case", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Wants to think through broader networking use case for Zo"}]}