{"entities": [{"name": "Michael", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Recipient at Johnson CMC, part of follow-up on Careerspan discussion"}, {"name": "Amanda", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Recipient at Johnson CMC, part of follow-up on Careerspan discussion"}, {"name": "Victoria", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Recipient at Johnson CMC, part of follow-up on Careerspan discussion"}, {"name": "Chase", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Recipient at Johnson CMC, part of follow-up on Careerspan discussion"}, {"name": "Diane", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact at Columbia SPS working with Careerspan in graduate program context"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company - career coaching platform for students"}, {"name": "Johnson CMC", "type": "ORG", "context": "Target school for Careerspan partnership discussion"}, {"name": "UMass Amherst", "type": "ORG", "context": "University with successful Careerspan deployment"}, {"name": "Eisenberg School of Management", "type": "ORG", "context": "Business school at UMass Amherst that deployed Careerspan with undergrad students"}, {"name": "Columbia SPS", "type": "ORG", "context": "Columbia School of Professional Studies, using Careerspan in graduate program"}, {"name": "structured reflection tool", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Use case for Careerspan with admits and pre-MBA summer work"}, {"name": "coach dashboard", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Careerspan feature highlighting student readiness and gaps"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Diane", "to": "Columbia SPS", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Working with Careerspan in graduate program context"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Eisenberg School of Management", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Deployed with undergrad business students, 92% strengthened presentation"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Columbia SPS", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Active partnership in graduate program context"}, {"from": "Eisenberg School of Management", "to": "UMass Amherst", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Business school within UMass Amherst"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "structured reflection tool", "type": "USES", "context": "Schools use Careerspan as reflection tool for admits"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "coach dashboard", "type": "USES", "context": "Feature showing student readiness and gaps"}]}