{"entities": [{"name": "Abby", "type": "PERSON", "context": "CEO of Season, female founder and immigrant founder, sports-passionate"}, {"name": "Season", "type": "ORG", "context": "B2B conversational AI company for sports, gaming, media & entertainment fan engagement"}, {"name": "YC", "type": "ORG", "context": "Y Combinator - accelerator Season applied to, co-founder is YC voice AI expert"}, {"name": "Decagon", "type": "ORG", "context": "Comparison company for Season's positioning"}, {"name": "Intercom", "type": "ORG", "context": "Comparison company for Season's positioning"}, {"name": "Salesforce", "type": "ORG", "context": "CDP market player Season is targeting"}, {"name": "Braze", "type": "ORG", "context": "CDP market player Season is targeting"}, {"name": "Klaviyo", "type": "ORG", "context": "CDP market player Season is targeting"}, {"name": "Conversational AI for fan engagement", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Season's core product - AI for sports/gaming community building"}, {"name": "CDP market", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Customer Data Platform market - Season's target space in non-ecommerce"}, {"name": "Female founder community", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Community Abby identifies with and wants to support"}, {"name": "Immigrant founder community", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Community Abby identifies with and wants to support"}, {"name": "YC application", "type": "EVENT", "context": "Just finished, Abby 'crashed out super hard' after completing it"}, {"name": "Precede round fundraising", "type": "EVENT", "context": "$1.5M target, half committed, seeking lead"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Abby", "to": "Season", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "CEO and leader of the company"}, {"from": "Season", "to": "Conversational AI for fan engagement", "type": "USES", "context": "Core product offering for sports, gaming, media & entertainment"}, {"from": "Season", "to": "CDP market", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Positioning like Decagon/Intercom but for CDP market in non-ecommerce"}, {"from": "Season", "to": "Decagon", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Comparable company in different market"}, {"from": "Season", "to": "Intercom", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Comparable company in different market"}, {"from": "Abby", "to": "Female founder community", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Mission-driven about leveling playing field"}, {"from": "Abby", "to": "Immigrant founder community", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Wants to help others have same privilege"}, {"from": "Season", "to": "YC", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Applied to YC, co-founder is YC voice AI expert"}, {"from": "Abby", "to": "YC application", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Just finished application, worked intensely on it"}]}