{"entities": [{"name": "Vrijen", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Primary actor; founder of Careerspan coordinating multiple strategic conversations"}, {"name": "David", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Associated with Superposition; involved in commission boundary clarification"}, {"name": "Camina", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Has a loosely defined existing agreement with V; needs reset conversation about exit outcome"}, {"name": "V's father", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Family member who could potentially provide short-term bridge funding"}, {"name": "Amanda", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Potential source of bridge funding alongside V's father"}, {"name": "Logan", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Partner involved in post-exit planning with Vrijen"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company; central to commission boundary and exit discussions"}, {"name": "Superposition", "type": "ORG", "context": "David's organization; involved in recruiter relationship and commission discussions"}, {"name": "Commission boundary", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Clarification needed to avoid double-counting or undermining recruiter relationships"}, {"name": "Short bridge", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Contingency financial lever (one extra month of salaries) for improving exit deal"}, {"name": "Post-exit rest period", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Planned decompression time as psychological reward after the grind"}, {"name": "Puerto Rico race", "type": "EVENT", "context": "Potential post-exit activity for motivation"}, {"name": "Mexico/Colombia decompression trip", "type": "EVENT", "context": "Potential post-exit travel for recovery"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Founder managing exit negotiations and strategic relationships"}, {"from": "David", "to": "Superposition", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "David is associated with Superposition organization"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "David", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Coordinating on commission boundary clarification"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Superposition", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Commission boundary and recruiter relationship overlap"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Camina", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Has existing loosely defined agreement requiring reset conversation"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "V's father", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Family member as potential contingency funding source"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Amanda", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Potential contingency funding source"}, {"from": "Logan", "to": "Vrijen", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Collaborating on post-exit planning"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Short bridge", "type": "USES", "context": "Contingency lever to be pulled only if better deal is within reach"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Post-exit rest period", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Important for motivation and aligning expectations with partners/family"}]}