{"entities": [{"name": "Tiffany", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Collaborator with high-trust, collaborative dynamic with Vrijen"}, {"name": "Vrijen", "type": "PERSON", "context": "V, the primary person in this knowledge system"}, {"name": "Ben", "type": "PERSON", "context": "External stakeholder involved in content creation (talk, possible course)"}, {"name": "Tejas", "type": "PERSON", "context": "External stakeholder at varying level of engagement"}, {"name": "David", "type": "PERSON", "context": "External stakeholder with networking expertise, involved in product co-design"}, {"name": "Next Play", "type": "ORG", "context": "Distribution channel for Zo"}, {"name": "AI Collective", "type": "ORG", "context": "Distribution channel for Zo"}, {"name": "Zo", "type": "ORG", "context": "Product/company needing to prove value via data-backed event performance"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Tiffany", "to": "Vrijen", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "High-trust collaborative dynamic with room for candid brainstorming and strategic critique"}, {"from": "Ben", "to": "Zo", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Content partnership - talk and possible course development"}, {"from": "David", "to": "Zo", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Product co-design leveraging networking expertise"}, {"from": "Zo", "to": "Next Play", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Distribution partnership opportunity"}, {"from": "Zo", "to": "AI Collective", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Distribution partnership opportunity"}]}