{"entities": [{"name": "Malvika", "type": "PERSON", "context": "HR professional who provided insights on community dynamics and uses Boardy"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company, pursuing community partnership strategy for talent access"}, {"name": "Boardy", "type": "ORG", "context": "Competitor platform for warm intros, gaining momentum Q1 2025"}, {"name": "Women Shaping AI", "type": "ORG", "context": "Community with 170 members, example of high-trust distribution channel"}, {"name": "Transform", "type": "ORG", "context": "HR community with talent acquisition focus, free to join"}, {"name": "People Over Perks", "type": "ORG", "context": "HR community mentioned by Malvika"}, {"name": "Culture Geeks", "type": "ORG", "context": "HR community mentioned by Malvika"}, {"name": "Talent Collective", "type": "ORG", "context": "HR community mentioned by Malvika"}, {"name": "OGC", "type": "ORG", "context": "HR community mentioned by Malvika"}, {"name": "Employee Connect", "type": "ORG", "context": "HR community mentioned by Malvika"}, {"name": "Community-Embedded Distribution", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Belief that niche high-trust communities outperform cold channels for distribution"}, {"name": "HR Communities as High-Signal Aggregators", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Insight that HR communities centralize decision-makers, enabling efficient ICP saturation"}, {"name": "Narrative Depth vs Simple Matching", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Differentiation strategy for Careerspan against Boardy's approach"}, {"name": "Q1 2025 Boardy Inflection", "type": "EVENT", "context": "When Boardy started getting quality intros after 6 months of low activity"}, {"name": "Fall 2024", "type": "EVENT", "context": "When Malvika started using Boardy"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Malvika", "to": "Boardy", "type": "USES", "context": "Started using fall 2024, began getting intros Q1 2025"}, {"from": "Malvika", "to": "Transform", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Mentioned as key community where you meet similar HR professionals"}, {"from": "Malvika", "to": "People Over Perks", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Identified as key HR community"}, {"from": "Malvika", "to": "Culture Geeks", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Identified as key HR community"}, {"from": "Malvika", "to": "Talent Collective", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Identified as key HR community"}, {"from": "Malvika", "to": "OGC", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Identified as key HR community"}, {"from": "Malvika", "to": "Employee Connect", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Identified as key HR community"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Community-Embedded Distribution", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Core strategy validated by 85-90% email open rates"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Women Shaping AI", "type": "USES", "context": "Partnership channel expected to drive higher engagement than mass outreach"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Narrative Depth vs Simple Matching", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Positioning strategy to differentiate from Boardy before market consolidation"}, {"from": "Boardy", "to": "Q1 2025 Boardy Inflection", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Platform hit inflection point with accelerating traction"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Boardy", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Competitor relationship with compressing window for differentiation"}]}