{"entities": [{"name": "Logan", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Collaborator discussing pipeline and community strategy with V; posts Careerspan job board in communities"}, {"name": "V", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder of Careerspan, coordinating job board expansion and community outreach"}, {"name": "Liam", "type": "PERSON", "context": "From Transcend Network, previously expressed interest in Careerspan for his recruiting platform"}, {"name": "Brady", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Person Liam had spoken with about Careerspan"}, {"name": "Marvin", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Has jobs that need to be pulled into Careerspan job board"}, {"name": "Ilsa", "type": "PERSON", "context": "V needs to coordinate with her about integrating roles"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company with job board and story-based candidate platform"}, {"name": "Transcend Network", "type": "ORG", "context": "Network whose alumni (now in operating roles) may be promising segment for Careerspan"}, {"name": "Next Play", "type": "ORG", "context": "Community where Logan posts Careerspan job board links, seeing solid engagement"}, {"name": "Story depth hypothesis", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "~80% of candidates who complete one story go on to complete a second"}, {"name": "Pipeline and community strategy", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Broader strategic approach leveraging communities and alumni networks"}, {"name": "Job board", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Careerspan's expanding job board with roles from multiple sources"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Logan", "to": "V", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Zoom out together to discuss broader pipeline and community strategy"}, {"from": "Liam", "to": "Transcend Network", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Liam is from the Transcend Network"}, {"from": "Liam", "to": "Brady", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Liam had once spoken with Brady about Careerspan"}, {"from": "Liam", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Expressed interest in Careerspan for his recruiting platform"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Ilsa", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "V needs to coordinate with Ilsa about integrating roles"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Marvin", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Jobs from Marvin need to be pulled into job board"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Job board", "type": "USES", "context": "Careerspan has a growing job board with expanding roles"}, {"from": "Logan", "to": "Next Play", "type": "USES", "context": "Logan posts Careerspan job board links into Next Play community"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Story depth hypothesis", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Data showing 80% second-story completion matches their hypothesis"}, {"from": "Transcend Network", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Transcend alumni in operating roles identified as promising segment"}]}