{"entities": [{"name": "Vrijen", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Owner of action items, founder of Careerspan"}, {"name": "Michael", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Person to be introduced to institutional references by Vrijen"}, {"name": "Diane", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact at Columbia SPS, serves as institutional reference"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company, career coaching platform with resume/story workflows"}, {"name": "UMass Eisenberg", "type": "ORG", "context": "Institution with existing Careerspan deployment, has survey results and usage stats"}, {"name": "Aspire", "type": "ORG", "context": "Institution with outcome summaries from Careerspan use"}, {"name": "Columbia SPS", "type": "ORG", "context": "Columbia School of Professional Studies, where Diane works"}, {"name": "Johnson", "type": "ORG", "context": "MBA program targeted for Careerspan rollout, focus on early and diversity recruiting"}, {"name": "CMC", "type": "ORG", "context": "Career Management Center, handles internal risk/compliance questions for Johnson"}, {"name": "Do not train flags", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Privacy mechanism for external LLM calls preventing model training on student data"}, {"name": "Student data ownership", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Principle that students own accounts and have deletion rights"}, {"name": "Stories to bullets to resumes workflow", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Key Careerspan workflow converting stories into resume content with coach view"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Founder and owner, responsible for institutional partnerships"}, {"from": "Diane", "to": "Columbia SPS", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Institutional contact who can serve as reference"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "UMass Eisenberg", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Existing deployment with measurable survey results and usage stats"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Aspire", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Existing institutional deployment with outcome summaries"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Johnson", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Proposed rollout target, onboarding concept being drafted"}, {"from": "CMC", "to": "Johnson", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Internal team requiring data/privacy documentation for compliance"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Michael", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Planning to introduce Michael to institutional references"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Do not train flags", "type": "USES", "context": "Privacy control for external LLM API calls"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Student data ownership", "type": "USES", "context": "Core privacy stance giving students account control and deletion rights"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Stories to bullets to resumes workflow", "type": "USES", "context": "Primary content generation workflow for students"}]}