{"entities": [{"name": "Vrijen", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder of Careerspan who positioned the company as quality over quantity channel"}, {"name": "Mai", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Lensa contact willing to test partnership and assign dedicated analysts"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company - boutique talent network with high engagement rates (75-80% email open, 15-16% CTR)"}, {"name": "Lensa", "type": "ORG", "context": "Scale distribution partner with access to 25M jobs and established ATS/agency relationships"}, {"name": "AppCast", "type": "ORG", "context": "Technical integration partner providing clean handoff with minimal engineering lift"}, {"name": "McKinsey", "type": "ORG", "context": "Source of elite alumni talent for Careerspan network"}, {"name": "Google", "type": "ORG", "context": "Source of elite employee talent for Careerspan network"}, {"name": "Ivy League", "type": "ORG", "context": "Source of elite graduate talent for Careerspan network"}, {"name": "Supply-demand arbitrage partnership", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Framework describing Careerspan-Lensa strategic alignment"}, {"name": "Quality over quantity", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Vrijen's positioning strategy emphasizing engagement rates and candidate quality over volume"}, {"name": "Passive candidates", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Always job-ready users with 2-3% monthly reactivation rate - dormant but ready to engage"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Founder who positioned the company strategically"}, {"from": "Mai", "to": "Lensa", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Lensa representative handling partnership testing"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Lensa", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Strategic partnership for supply-demand arbitrage"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "AppCast", "type": "USES", "context": "Technical integration for job distribution"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "McKinsey", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Sources talent from McKinsey alumni network"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Google", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Sources talent from Google employee network"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Ivy League", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Sources talent from Ivy League graduate network"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Quality over quantity", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Core positioning strategy for Careerspan partnerships"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Passive candidates", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Key value proposition - engaged but not actively job-searching users"}]}