{"entities": [{"name": "Marvin", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Has roles that need to be imported into the Careerspan job board"}, {"name": "Rahul", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Associated with Zeni for 1099 processing setup"}, {"name": "Erica", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Promising relationship that could convert to revenue or distribution"}, {"name": "Davide", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Promising relationship that could convert to revenue or distribution"}, {"name": "Davis", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Promising relationship that could convert to revenue or distribution"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company with a job board needing job imports and workflow alignment"}, {"name": "Zeni", "type": "ORG", "context": "Handles 1099 processing and filing for tax compliance"}, {"name": "Darwinbox", "type": "ORG", "context": "Promising relationship that could convert to revenue or distribution"}, {"name": "Marvin job imports", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Mechanism to pull Marvin's roles into the Careerspan job board"}, {"name": "1099 processing", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Tax document generation and filing setup with Zeni"}, {"name": "Job board", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Careerspan's job listing platform where roles appear"}, {"name": "Compliance workflows", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Workflows that need alignment with JDs and job board"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Rahul", "to": "Zeni", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Rahul is the contact at Zeni for 1099 processing confirmation"}, {"from": "Marvin job imports", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Imports pull Marvin's roles into the Careerspan job board"}, {"from": "Zeni", "to": "1099 processing", "type": "USES", "context": "Zeni generates and files 1099s for tax compliance"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Job board", "type": "USES", "context": "Careerspan operates the job board where roles appear"}, {"from": "Job board", "to": "Compliance workflows", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Job board and JDs need alignment with compliance workflows"}]}