{"entities": [{"name": "Logan", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Collaborator handling LLX pitch, FutureFit AI outreach, and David Fano call prep for Careerspan"}, {"name": "Vrijen", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Careerspan founder drafting job board post templates"}, {"name": "David Fano", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact with upcoming call about Careerspan strategic direction"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company - subject of sales pitches and potential acquisition conversations"}, {"name": "LLX", "type": "ORG", "context": "Organization receiving pitch from Logan on 2025-12-11"}, {"name": "FutureFit AI", "type": "ORG", "context": "Potential acquirer/partner being re-engaged"}, {"name": "Superposition", "type": "ORG", "context": "Part of recruiting network showing interest in Careerspan"}, {"name": "Matchbox", "type": "ORG", "context": "Part of recruiting network showing interest in Careerspan"}, {"name": "Coffee Space", "type": "ORG", "context": "Part of recruiting network showing interest in Careerspan"}, {"name": "Job board", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Careerspan product with traction, needs daily highlighted role posts"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Logan", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Handling sales pitches and strategic conversations for the company"}, {"from": "Logan", "to": "LLX", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Delivering pitch as rehearsal for crisp storytelling about Careerspan"}, {"from": "Logan", "to": "Vrijen", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Collaborating on Careerspan go-to-market and strategic exit prep"}, {"from": "FutureFit AI", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Potential acquirer/partner - unclear if serious or cheapskate"}, {"from": "David Fano", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Strategic call about raising vs. strategic exit options"}, {"from": "Superposition", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Recruiting network interest as reference point for momentum"}, {"from": "Matchbox", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Recruiting network interest as reference point for momentum"}, {"from": "Coffee Space", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Recruiting network interest as reference point for momentum"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Job board", "type": "USES", "context": "Creating reusable daily post template for highlighted roles"}]}