{"entities": [{"name": "Medrock AI", "type": "ORG", "context": "Healthcare AI company with operational bottlenecks around consent-calling"}, {"name": "GiveWell", "type": "ORG", "context": "Organization hosting a session on community programming roadmap"}, {"name": "US Army FUSE", "type": "ORG", "context": "Military innovation program; hosting upcoming session for dual-use/defense founders"}, {"name": "Alex", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Healthcare Entrepreneur-in-Residence; point of contact for healthcare founders"}, {"name": "Daniel", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder raising capital; to leverage group for investor intros"}, {"name": "Lance", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder raising capital; to leverage group for investor intros"}, {"name": "Abby", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder raising capital; to leverage group for investor intros"}, {"name": "Felix", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder raising capital; to leverage group for investor intros"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company; resource for operators needing hiring or narrative help"}, {"name": "V", "type": "PERSON", "context": "The person whose knowledge system this is; founder of Careerspan"}, {"name": "Entrepreneur-in-Residence", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Launch of EIR model starting with healthcare vertical"}], "relationships": [{"from": "V", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "V is the founder of Careerspan"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Alex", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Collaboration on healthcare EIR model"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Daniel", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Founder raising capital; V providing guidance on investor intros"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Lance", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Founder raising capital; V providing guidance on investor intros"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Abby", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Founder raising capital; V providing guidance on investor intros"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Felix", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Founder raising capital; V providing guidance on investor intros"}, {"from": "Alex", "to": "Entrepreneur-in-Residence", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Alex serves as healthcare EIR under this model"}, {"from": "US Army FUSE", "to": "Entrepreneur-in-Residence", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Part of community programming events under EIR model"}]}