{"entities": [{"name": "Malvika", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact coordinating deliverables including HR community links, Women Shaping AI code, and Logan intro"}, {"name": "Logan", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Co-founder (likely of Careerspan), coordinating Boston conference appearance and workshop delivery"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company, referred to as 'Careerspan team' managing deliverables"}, {"name": "Women Shaping AI", "type": "ORG", "context": "Community receiving dedicated code, co-hosting workshop with Logan"}, {"name": "Transform", "type": "ORG", "context": "HR community with invitation links promised by Malvika"}, {"name": "People Over Perks", "type": "ORG", "context": "HR community with invitation links promised by Malvika"}, {"name": "Culture Geeks", "type": "ORG", "context": "HR community with invitation links promised by Malvika"}, {"name": "Talent Collective", "type": "ORG", "context": "HR community with invitation links promised by Malvika"}, {"name": "OGC", "type": "ORG", "context": "HR community with invitation links promised by Malvika"}, {"name": "Employee Connect", "type": "ORG", "context": "HR community with invitation links promised by Malvika"}, {"name": "Boston AI-Powered Women's Conference", "type": "EVENT", "context": "Conference around which Logan intro and workshop are being coordinated, likely September 2025"}, {"name": "Workshop", "type": "EVENT", "context": "Planned delivery by Logan with Women Shaping AI, format/timing TBD"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Malvika", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Coordinating deliverables and community introductions"}, {"from": "Logan", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Co-founder of the company"}, {"from": "Logan", "to": "Workshop", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Will deliver the workshop"}, {"from": "Women Shaping AI", "to": "Workshop", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Co-hosting workshop with Logan"}, {"from": "Workshop", "to": "Boston AI-Powered Women's Conference", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Workshop timing coordinated around the conference"}, {"from": "Malvika", "to": "Women Shaping AI", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Providing dedicated code for the community"}, {"from": "Malvika", "to": "Transform", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Has invitation links to share"}, {"from": "Malvika", "to": "People Over Perks", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Has invitation links to share"}, {"from": "Malvika", "to": "Culture Geeks", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Has invitation links to share"}, {"from": "Malvika", "to": "Talent Collective", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Has invitation links to share"}, {"from": "Malvika", "to": "OGC", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Has invitation links to share"}, {"from": "Malvika", "to": "Employee Connect", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Has invitation links to share"}]}