{"entities": [{"name": "Vrijen", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder of Careerspan, exploring acquisition/acqui-hire paths while pushing GTM"}, {"name": "Kamina", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Advisor/collaborator with credibility and relationships at ASA and Strada; will activate intros and invite Vrijen to events"}, {"name": "Jane", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact at ASA whom Kamina will reach out to for partnership/funding conversations"}, {"name": "Darren", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact at Strada whom Kamina will reach out to for partnership/funding conversations"}, {"name": "ASA", "type": "ORG", "context": "Priority strategic acquirer/funder target; controls meaningful capital, cares about student outcomes especially for HBCUs"}, {"name": "Strada", "type": "ORG", "context": "Priority strategic acquirer/funder target; controls meaningful capital, cares about student outcomes especially for HBCUs"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company; subject of acquisition/funding exploration and GTM activities"}, {"name": "HBCUs", "type": "ORG", "context": "Historically Black Colleges and Universities; underserved institutions that ASA and Strada care about"}, {"name": "Mount Saint Vincent", "type": "ORG", "context": "Institution hosting upcoming event relevant for GTM and BD"}, {"name": "BMCC", "type": "ORG", "context": "Institution hosting upcoming event relevant for GTM and BD"}, {"name": "St. Peter's", "type": "ORG", "context": "Institution hosting upcoming event relevant for GTM and BD"}, {"name": "Exit strategy", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "General orientation toward creating a good exit for team and advisors via acquisition or acqui-hire"}, {"name": "GTM", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Go-to-market strategy using events as platforms to seed pilots and deepen relationships"}, {"name": "Acqui-hire", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Acquisition path being explored alongside traditional acquisition"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Kamina", "to": "Jane", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Kamina has relationship with Jane at ASA and will activate intro"}, {"from": "Kamina", "to": "Darren", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Kamina has relationship with Darren at Strada and will activate intro"}, {"from": "Kamina", "to": "Vrijen", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Kamina advising on strategy, activating intros, inviting to events"}, {"from": "Kamina", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Keeping Careerspan in mind for upcoming events at institutions"}, {"from": "ASA", "to": "HBCUs", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "ASA cares about student outcomes especially for HBCUs and underserved institutions"}, {"from": "Strada", "to": "HBCUs", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Strada cares about student outcomes especially for HBCUs and underserved institutions"}, {"from": "ASA", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "ASA already knows Kamina and/or Careerspan; prioritized as acquisition/funding target"}, {"from": "Strada", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Strada already knows Kamina and/or Careerspan; prioritized as acquisition/funding target"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Exit strategy", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Continuing to explore exit paths with intent of creating good exit for team and advisors"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "GTM", "type": "USES", "context": "Using upcoming events as GTM and BD platforms to seed pilots"}]}