{"entities": [{"name": "Vrijen", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Owner of Careerspan, orchestrating hiring funnel and candidate distribution"}, {"name": "Alan", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Client receiving JD processing, application link, and introduction to Shivam"}, {"name": "Shivam", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Works at Corridor X dev shop, being connected to Alan for technical scoping"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company providing AI-led candidate assessment and hiring funnel services"}, {"name": "Corridor X", "type": "ORG", "context": "Dev shop where Shivam works, for technical scoping work"}, {"name": "Melly", "type": "ORG", "context": "Company for which Alan is hiring, kept anonymous in role distribution"}, {"name": "Future of Higher Education Group", "type": "ORG", "context": "Community channel for distributing anonymous role postings"}, {"name": "Next Play", "type": "ORG", "context": "Community channel for distributing anonymous role postings"}, {"name": "AI-led assessment", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Careerspan's assessment system with question flow, story prompts, and scoring dimensions"}, {"name": "Application link", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Anonymous candidate-facing link for self-reflection exercise completion"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Vrijen is the owner of Careerspan"}, {"from": "Shivam", "to": "Corridor X", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Shivam works at the Corridor X dev shop"}, {"from": "Alan", "to": "Melly", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Alan is hiring for Melly but keeping the company anonymous"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Alan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "V is orchestrating Alan's hiring funnel and connecting him to resources"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Shivam", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "V is setting up group chat to connect Alan with Shivam"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "AI-led assessment", "type": "USES", "context": "Careerspan configures AI-led assessments for candidate evaluation"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Future of Higher Education Group", "type": "USES", "context": "Channel for distributing curated role postings"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Next Play", "type": "USES", "context": "Channel for distributing curated role postings"}]}