{"entities": [{"name": "UMass Amherst", "type": "ORG", "context": "Eisenberg undergrad business program; early adopter showing strong proof points (~92% students reported Careerspan strengthened experiences)"}, {"name": "Rice", "type": "ORG", "context": "Institution in play for Careerspan; good fit for early career prep use case"}, {"name": "Columbia SPS", "type": "ORG", "context": "Columbia School of Professional Studies; familiar with product but adoption slower than ideal"}, {"name": "Cornell Johnson", "type": "ORG", "context": "MBA program re-engaging after two-year gap to consider Careerspan for resume/storytelling"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company; career reflection and storytelling platform for students"}, {"name": "Felix", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact at Rice; had positive conversation about Careerspan"}, {"name": "Jim Pike", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact at Rice; part of positive conversation about Careerspan fit"}, {"name": "Diane", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact at Columbia SPS; familiar with the product"}, {"name": "confidence lift", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Outcome reported by UMass students after using Careerspan"}, {"name": "depth of reflection", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Quality students reported strong satisfaction with at UMass"}, {"name": "resume/storytelling platform", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "How Cornell Johnson frames potential Careerspan adoption"}], "relationships": [{"from": "UMass Amherst", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "USES", "context": "Deployed in Eisenberg undergrad business with strong results"}, {"from": "Felix", "to": "Rice", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Contact involved in Careerspan conversation"}, {"from": "Jim Pike", "to": "Rice", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Contact involved in Careerspan conversation"}, {"from": "Diane", "to": "Columbia SPS", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Careerspan relationship contact"}, {"from": "Rice", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "In play for early career prep use case"}, {"from": "Columbia SPS", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Existing relationship; adoption slower than ideal"}, {"from": "Cornell Johnson", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Re-engaging after two-year gap for resume/storytelling platform"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "confidence lift", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Outcome delivered to UMass students"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "depth of reflection", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Core value proposition validated at UMass"}]}