{"entities": [{"name": "Kamina", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Collaborator who details institutional barriers, has contacts at ASA and Strada, provides tactical GTM advice"}, {"name": "Vrijen", "type": "PERSON", "context": "V, founder of Careerspan, discussing acquisition and partnership strategy"}, {"name": "Jane", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact at ASA whom Kamina will reach out to"}, {"name": "Darren", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact at Strada whom Kamina will reach out to"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company, subject of acquisition discussions with ASA and Strada"}, {"name": "ASA", "type": "ORG", "context": "Prime acquisition/funding candidate for Careerspan"}, {"name": "Strada", "type": "ORG", "context": "Prime acquisition/funding candidate for Careerspan"}, {"name": "CUNY", "type": "ORG", "context": "Institution that refused to pay nominal costs or promote events"}, {"name": "Columbia", "type": "ORG", "context": "Institution that refused support; also target for email blast"}, {"name": "NYU", "type": "ORG", "context": "Institution that refused to pay or promote events"}, {"name": "Rice", "type": "ORG", "context": "Target institution for email blast campaign"}, {"name": "UMass", "type": "ORG", "context": "Target for email blast; has results to highlight"}, {"name": "Cornell", "type": "ORG", "context": "Target institution for email blast campaign"}, {"name": "HBCUs", "type": "ORG", "context": "Historically Black colleges identified as mission-aligned opportunity"}, {"name": "Per Scholas", "type": "ORG", "context": "National workforce program that needs Careerspan's offerings"}, {"name": "COOP", "type": "ORG", "context": "National workforce program identified as opportunity"}, {"name": "Institutional indictment", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Framework that institutions, not students, are the bottleneck to adoption"}, {"name": "Acquisition vector", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Strategy identifying ASA and Strada as funding/acquisition paths"}, {"name": "Go-to-market email blast", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Concrete tactic: email naming schools and highlighting UMass results"}, {"name": "Concrete reciprocity", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "V's commitment to not profit before Kamina does; commission structure"}, {"name": "Email blast campaign", "type": "EVENT", "context": "Planned outreach to Rice, Columbia, UMass, Cornell with tactical omissions"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Kamina", "to": "Vrijen", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Financially aligned partner with commission structure for deals she catalyzes"}, {"from": "Kamina", "to": "Vrijen", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Provides tactical GTM advice including strategic school omissions to induce FOMO"}, {"from": "Kamina", "to": "Jane", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Direct contact at ASA; volunteered to reach out"}, {"from": "Kamina", "to": "Darren", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Direct contact at Strada; volunteered to reach out"}, {"from": "Jane", "to": "ASA", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Kamina's contact at ASA"}, {"from": "Darren", "to": "Strada", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Kamina's contact at Strada"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "ASA", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "ASA identified as prime acquisition/funding candidate"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Strada", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Strada identified as prime acquisition/funding candidate"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Concrete reciprocity", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Explicit commitment to not make money before Kamina does"}, {"from": "Kamina", "to": "HBCUs", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Has direct lines into key decision-makers at HBCUs"}, {"from": "Kamina", "to": "Per Scholas", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Has connections to national workforce programs"}, {"from": "Kamina", "to": "COOP", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Has connections to national workforce programs"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Go-to-market email blast", "type": "USES", "context": "Agreed concrete move converged on with Kamina"}]}