{"entities": [{"name": "Vrijen", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder of Careerspan, offered to deliver workshop for Next Play members"}, {"name": "Pam", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Next Play contact who affirmed product-market fit and committed to introducing Vrijen to Ben"}, {"name": "Ben", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Next Play leadership/founder relations, bi-coastal presence (San Francisco/Tel Aviv), influences partner/perk ecosystem"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company focused on coaching/career development"}, {"name": "Zo", "type": "ORG", "context": "AI infrastructure product positioned for early-stage founders (hiring stages 1-3)"}, {"name": "Next Play", "type": "ORG", "context": "Organization supporting founder wellbeing and operational success, has partner/perk ecosystem"}, {"name": "Granola", "type": "ORG", "context": "Existing Next Play perk partner"}, {"name": "Reflexity", "type": "ORG", "context": "Existing Next Play perk partner"}, {"name": "Product-market fit for early-stage founders", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Signal that founders in hiring stages 1-3 would find value in Zo's simplicity and affordability"}, {"name": "Founder wellbeing", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Part of Next Play's mission that aligns with Careerspan's coaching angle"}, {"name": "B01 Meeting", "type": "EVENT", "context": "Meeting where key decisions about Careerspan/Zo positioning and Next Play partnership were discussed"}, {"name": "Workshop for Next Play", "type": "EVENT", "context": "Proposed workshop delivery being explored as direct training or Zo as a perk"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Founder of the company"}, {"from": "Pam", "to": "Next Play", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Contact at Next Play who can facilitate introductions"}, {"from": "Ben", "to": "Next Play", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Leadership role in founder relations and partner ecosystem"}, {"from": "Pam", "to": "Vrijen", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Affirmed product-market fit, committed to warm introduction to Ben"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Zo", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Portfolio synergy between coaching/career development and AI infrastructure"}, {"from": "Zo", "to": "Next Play", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Potential positioning as perk for Next Play founders"}, {"from": "Granola", "to": "Next Play", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Existing perk partnership"}, {"from": "Reflexity", "to": "Next Play", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Existing perk partnership"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Ben", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Pending warm introduction via Pam"}]}