{"entities": [{"name": "Kamina", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Primary Champion with high energy, high belief, and strong networks; leads ASA, Strada, and national program conversations"}, {"name": "Vrijen", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Primary Operator owning product narrative, metrics, and coordination; runs email blast and school-side experiments"}, {"name": "Logan", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Collaborator whom Vrijen coordinates with"}, {"name": "Ilse", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Collaborator whom Vrijen coordinates with"}, {"name": "ASA", "type": "ORG", "context": "Capital/Acquirer target organization"}, {"name": "Strada", "type": "ORG", "context": "Capital/Acquirer target organization"}, {"name": "UMass", "type": "ORG", "context": "Market Credibility Anchor university"}, {"name": "Rice", "type": "ORG", "context": "Market Credibility Anchor university"}, {"name": "Columbia", "type": "ORG", "context": "Market Credibility Anchor university"}, {"name": "Cornell Johnson", "type": "ORG", "context": "Market Credibility Anchor business school"}, {"name": "Power Map", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Strategic framework summarizing key players, roles, and immediate unlocks"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Logan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Coordination on product and metrics"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Ilse", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Coordination on product and metrics"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Kamina", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Vrijen provides data-rich package while Kamina takes it to external conversations"}, {"from": "Kamina", "to": "ASA", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Taking data package into capital/acquirer conversations"}, {"from": "Kamina", "to": "Strada", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Taking data package into capital/acquirer conversations"}, {"from": "Kamina", "to": "UMass", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Student reviews from Kamina's events provide market credibility"}, {"from": "Kamina", "to": "Rice", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Student reviews from Kamina's events provide market credibility"}, {"from": "Kamina", "to": "Columbia", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Student reviews from Kamina's events provide market credibility"}, {"from": "Kamina", "to": "Cornell Johnson", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Student reviews from Kamina's events provide market credibility"}]}