{"entities": [{"name": "Malvika", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Collaborator providing HR community connections and competitive intelligence on Boardy"}, {"name": "Vrijen", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder of Careerspan, receiving strategic advice"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company targeting HR/talent acquisition professionals"}, {"name": "Boardy", "type": "ORG", "context": "Competitor that started Q1 2025, gaining momentum with intros after 6-month ramp"}, {"name": "Transform", "type": "ORG", "context": "HR community with high signal-to-noise ratio for decision-makers"}, {"name": "People Over Perks", "type": "ORG", "context": "HR community within target ICP"}, {"name": "Culture Geeks", "type": "ORG", "context": "HR community within target ICP"}, {"name": "Talent Collective", "type": "ORG", "context": "HR community within target ICP"}, {"name": "OGC", "type": "ORG", "context": "HR community within target ICP"}, {"name": "Employee Connect", "type": "ORG", "context": "HR community within target ICP"}, {"name": "ICP", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Ideal Customer Profile - HR/talent acquisition professionals"}, {"name": "Competitive Landscape Intelligence", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Strategic monitoring of competitors like Boardy for positioning insights"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Malvika", "to": "Vrijen", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Providing strategic input on HR communities and competitive landscape"}, {"from": "Malvika", "to": "Transform", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Has existing relationships enabling proxy entry for Careerspan"}, {"from": "Malvika", "to": "People Over Perks", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Has existing relationships enabling proxy entry for Careerspan"}, {"from": "Malvika", "to": "Culture Geeks", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Has existing relationships enabling proxy entry for Careerspan"}, {"from": "Malvika", "to": "Talent Collective", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Has existing relationships enabling proxy entry for Careerspan"}, {"from": "Malvika", "to": "OGC", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Has existing relationships enabling proxy entry for Careerspan"}, {"from": "Malvika", "to": "Employee Connect", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Has existing relationships enabling proxy entry for Careerspan"}, {"from": "Malvika", "to": "Boardy", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Personal experimentation with Boardy informed competitive intelligence"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Founder leading the company"}, {"from": "Boardy", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Competitor in similar space; differentiation window may be narrowing"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Competitive Landscape Intelligence", "type": "USES", "context": "Agreed to monitor Boardy positioning and traction"}]}