{"entities": [{"name": "Mihir", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Former sales leader at Dropbox and Asana, YC-backed founder, now co-founder at Invoice Butler"}, {"name": "Vrijen", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder of Careerspan, recently joined NYC Founder's Club"}, {"name": "Dropbox", "type": "ORG", "context": "Company where Mihir led ~15-person sales team from sub-$100M to IPO"}, {"name": "Asana", "type": "ORG", "context": "Company where Mihir led sales team through growth to IPO"}, {"name": "Y Combinator", "type": "ORG", "context": "Accelerator that backed Mihir's first company in 2016"}, {"name": "Invoice Butler", "type": "ORG", "context": "Mihir's current company, run to avoid VC dependency and stay close to profitability"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "Vrijen's company offering reflection product for candidates"}, {"name": "NYC Founder's Club", "type": "ORG", "context": "Trusted peer community for founders; Mihir member ~1 year, Vrijen recently joined"}, {"name": "No code until payment", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Mihir's rule from first company: validate demand with scrappy demos before building"}, {"name": "Bootstrap philosophy", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Avoiding VC dependency, customers pay before building, staying close to profitability"}, {"name": "Careerspan reflection product", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Helps candidates surface strengths in low-pressure environment with structured stories"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Mihir", "to": "Dropbox", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Led ~15-person sales team through growth to IPO"}, {"from": "Mihir", "to": "Asana", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Led sales team through growth to IPO"}, {"from": "Mihir", "to": "Y Combinator", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Founded YC-backed company in 2016 that was acquired"}, {"from": "Mihir", "to": "Invoice Butler", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Co-founder running company with bootstrap philosophy"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Founder of the company"}, {"from": "Mihir", "to": "No code until payment", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Core rule from first company applied at Invoice Butler"}, {"from": "Mihir", "to": "Bootstrap philosophy", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Avoiding VC dependency, insisting customers pay before building"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Mihir", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Collegial relationship, discussing potential Careerspan collaboration"}, {"from": "Mihir", "to": "NYC Founder's Club", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Member for about a year, finds it trusted confidential peer space"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "NYC Founder's Club", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Recently joined, attending first event soon"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Careerspan reflection product", "type": "USES", "context": "Product offering to help candidates demonstrate collaboration skills"}]}