{"entities": [{"name": "Vrijen Attawar", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder of Careerspan; primary owner of external relationships and enterprise pipeline"}, {"name": "Logan", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Teammate at Careerspan; V has deep trust with; at risk of burnout"}, {"name": "Ilsa", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Teammate at Careerspan; V has deep trust with; comfortable pushing back"}, {"name": "Erica", "type": "PERSON", "context": "External operator/prospect; has a developer community; V can credibly coach her"}, {"name": "Davide", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Prospect in promising conversations V wants to convert"}, {"name": "Davis", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Prospect in promising conversations V wants to convert"}, {"name": "Bradford", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Person whose company V is skeptical about due to lack of budget/brand value"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company; careers and narratives focused"}, {"name": "Darwinbox", "type": "ORG", "context": "Prospect/partner V wants to convert to revenue"}, {"name": "High-context collaboration", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Value V holds with teammates; honest communication about emotional state"}, {"name": "Distribution relationships", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Strategic approach V prefers over near-term cash; investing in relationships that create reach"}, {"name": "Stakeholder Intelligence", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Framework for understanding internal stakeholder dynamics"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Vrijen Attawar", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Founder; drives strategic decisions about prospects and partners"}, {"from": "Vrijen Attawar", "to": "Logan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Deep trust; comfortable airing doubts and pushing back"}, {"from": "Vrijen Attawar", "to": "Ilsa", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Deep trust; comfortable airing doubts and pushing back"}, {"from": "Vrijen Attawar", "to": "Erica", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Can credibly coach given background in careers and narratives"}, {"from": "Vrijen Attawar", "to": "High-context collaboration", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Values honest collaboration with teammates; open about emotional state"}, {"from": "Vrijen Attawar", "to": "Distribution relationships", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Willing to invest in relationships that create distribution rather than only near-term cash"}, {"from": "Erica", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Prospect with developer community that could provide distribution"}, {"from": "Logan", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Teammate carrying operational load"}, {"from": "Ilsa", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Teammate who provides pushback and collaboration"}]}