{"entities": [{"name": "Hannah", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Representative from Healthy Gamer who articulates research needs and measurement approaches"}, {"name": "V", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Vrijen, founder of Careerspan, describes product motion and cites hiring research"}, {"name": "Healthy Gamer", "type": "ORG", "context": "Organization seeking external outcomes research on its coaching programs"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company providing job-fit analytics and candidate-JD mapping"}, {"name": "Princeton", "type": "ORG", "context": "University co-authoring study on AI-generated resumes and hiring signal"}, {"name": "Dartmouth", "type": "ORG", "context": "University co-authoring study on AI-generated resumes and hiring signal"}, {"name": "Amherst", "type": "ORG", "context": "University mentioned as potential research population source"}, {"name": "Eisenberg", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Mentioned alongside Amherst as contact for student research population"}, {"name": "PROMIS", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Measurement scales for life purpose, anxiety, and depression used by Healthy Gamer"}, {"name": "IGD", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Previous measurement scale used by Healthy Gamer"}, {"name": "GAD-7", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Previous anxiety measurement scale"}, {"name": "PHQ-9", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Previous depression measurement scale"}, {"name": "Job-fit analytics", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Careerspan's value proposition mapping candidates against job descriptions"}, {"name": "Outcomes research", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "External validation research on coaching program effectiveness"}, {"name": "Degraded hiring signal", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Finding that AI-generated resumes cause ~15% higher mis-hiring rates"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Hannah", "to": "Healthy Gamer", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Hannah represents Healthy Gamer in discussing research needs"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "V is founder describing Careerspan's evolved product motion"}, {"from": "Healthy Gamer", "to": "PROMIS", "type": "USES", "context": "Evolved measurement stack for coaching outcomes"}, {"from": "Healthy Gamer", "to": "Outcomes research", "type": "USES", "context": "Seeking external validation of coaching programs"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Job-fit analytics", "type": "USES", "context": "Core value proposition for candidate assessment"}, {"from": "Princeton", "to": "Degraded hiring signal", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Co-authored study on AI resume impact"}, {"from": "Dartmouth", "to": "Degraded hiring signal", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Co-authored study on AI resume impact"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Degraded hiring signal", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Cites study to anchor business case for deeper assessment"}, {"from": "Eisenberg", "to": "Amherst", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Contact at Amherst for student research population"}]}