{"entities": [{"name": "Davit", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Job seeker who has submitted ~250 applications and maintains ~8 CV versions; committing to use Careerspan more actively"}, {"name": "V", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Careerspan representative making commitments to help Davit with introductions and advocacy"}, {"name": "Holly", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact V will re-engage about Deep Tune opportunity"}, {"name": "Ali", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact at True Meter that V will message on Davit's behalf"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "Platform with resume generator and story/role analysis features for job seekers"}, {"name": "Deep Tune", "type": "ORG", "context": "Company/role Davit is pursuing; Holly is a relevant contact"}, {"name": "True Meter", "type": "ORG", "context": "Company where Ali works; one of Davit's target roles"}, {"name": "Zo", "type": "ORG", "context": "Company whose founders V will advocate to once Davit's role analysis is strong"}, {"name": "Resume generator", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Careerspan feature that creates semantically tailored resumes aligned with job descriptions"}, {"name": "Application fatigue", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Exhaustion from customizing resumes for every application; problem Careerspan aims to solve"}], "relationships": [{"from": "V", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "V describes and represents Careerspan's features to job seekers"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Davit", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "V is helping Davit with job search strategy and making introductions"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Holly", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "V will re-engage Holly about Deep Tune opportunity for Davit"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Ali", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "V will message Ali at True Meter on Davit's behalf"}, {"from": "Ali", "to": "True Meter", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Ali is a contact at True Meter"}, {"from": "Davit", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "USES", "context": "Davit commits to adding stories and running role analyses through the platform"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Resume generator", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Resume generator is a core Careerspan feature"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Zo", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "V will advocate to Zo founders for Davit"}, {"from": "Davit", "to": "Deep Tune", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Deep Tune is one of Davit's target roles"}, {"from": "Davit", "to": "True Meter", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "True Meter is one of Davit's target roles"}, {"from": "Holly", "to": "Deep Tune", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Holly is the relevant contact for Deep Tune opportunity"}]}