{"entities": [{"name": "V", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Owner of tasks, advocating for candidates and curating Careerspan job board"}, {"name": "Holly", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact at Deep Tune, prior scheduling issues to acknowledge"}, {"name": "Davit", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Strong candidate being positioned for multiple AI-native/backend roles, has resume and Careerspan narratives"}, {"name": "Ali", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact at True Meter to message about Davit"}, {"name": "Deep Tune", "type": "ORG", "context": "Company where Holly works, target for Davit placement"}, {"name": "True Meter", "type": "ORG", "context": "Company with AI-native backend roles, Ali is contact there"}, {"name": "Zo Computer", "type": "ORG", "context": "Has infrastructure role and founders V can recommend to"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company producing candidate narratives and analyses, has job board"}, {"name": "Marvin Ventures", "type": "ORG", "context": "Partner organization with roles matching Davit's profile"}, {"name": "Careerspan narratives", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Candidate analysis output used to advocate for placements"}, {"name": "Careerspan job board", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Platform V curates with roles for candidates like Davit"}], "relationships": [{"from": "V", "to": "Holly", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Re-engaging to schedule call/interview for Davit"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Davit", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Advocating and positioning Davit for multiple roles"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Ali", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Will message about Davit for True Meter roles"}, {"from": "Holly", "to": "Deep Tune", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Contact for scheduling interviews at Deep Tune"}, {"from": "Ali", "to": "True Meter", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Contact for AI-native backend roles"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Founder, produces narratives and curates job board"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Careerspan job board", "type": "USES", "context": "Curating roles matching Davit's profile"}, {"from": "Davit", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "USES", "context": "Produces Careerspan output and analyses for advocacy"}, {"from": "Marvin Ventures", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Partner providing roles for job board"}]}