{"entities": [{"name": "Deep Tune", "type": "ORG", "context": "AI/engineering company offering visa sponsorship; V's primary near-term target for Davit"}, {"name": "Yarn", "type": "ORG", "context": "Company initially interesting but ruled out due to lack of visa sponsorship"}, {"name": "True Meter", "type": "ORG", "context": "Company hiring multiple AI-native backend engineers"}, {"name": "Zo Computer", "type": "ORG", "context": "Consumer-facing AI product company with infrastructure role V is excited about"}, {"name": "Warmer Jobs", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Paid tool for surfacing job opportunities via first-degree LinkedIn network"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company; proposed to use alongside Warmer Jobs"}, {"name": "Holly", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Recruiter associated with Deep Tune opportunity"}, {"name": "Marvin Ventures", "type": "ORG", "context": "Venture firm funneling candidates to Deep Tune"}, {"name": "Ali", "type": "PERSON", "context": "V's direct contact at True Meter"}, {"name": "Davit", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Job seeker V is advising; candidate for Deep Tune and True Meter"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Holly", "to": "Deep Tune", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Recruiter funneling candidates to Deep Tune"}, {"from": "Marvin Ventures", "to": "Deep Tune", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Venture firm channeling candidates to Deep Tune"}, {"from": "Ali", "to": "True Meter", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "V's direct contact at the company"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Ali", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Direct contact relationship for True Meter referrals"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Davit", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Helping with job search, offering discount codes and recommendations"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Zo Computer", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Has strong founder relationships; sees as high-leverage option"}, {"from": "Warmer Jobs", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Complementary tools proposed for use together"}]}