{"entities": [{"name": "Logan", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Team member experiencing exhaustion and difficulty focusing, taking offline break from Careerspan"}, {"name": "V", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder of Careerspan, encouraging Logan to take break"}, {"name": "Erica", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Former Google DevRel, recently laid off, had debrief meeting"}, {"name": "Davide", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Associated with multiple roles and JD A/B testing at Careerspan"}, {"name": "Davis", "type": "PERSON", "context": "High-potential prospect, associated with TeamWork Online"}, {"name": "Bradford", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Prospect being deprioritized, associated with K-12/AR software company"}, {"name": "Rahul", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Coordinates with Zeni for 1099 processing"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company, focus of job board and prospect work"}, {"name": "Google", "type": "ORG", "context": "Erica's former employer, DevRel team"}, {"name": "Transcend", "type": "ORG", "context": "Community with alumni network, edtech hiring slowdown context"}, {"name": "Next Play", "type": "ORG", "context": "Community used for distribution"}, {"name": "TeamWork Online", "type": "ORG", "context": "Company associated with Davis, upcoming high-potential call"}, {"name": "Darwinbox", "type": "ORG", "context": "High-potential prospect, upcoming call"}, {"name": "Zeni", "type": "ORG", "context": "Handles 1099 processing for back-office compliance"}, {"name": "Burnout", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Logan's current state requiring real break"}, {"name": "JD A/B testing", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Testing approach with separate Notion pages for each JD variant"}, {"name": "Prospect triage", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Prioritization process for upcoming calls"}, {"name": "Job board performance", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Early traction metrics showing ~80% story completion rate"}, {"name": "Crystal ball", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Tool to be sent to Erica in follow-up"}, {"name": "Detector", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Tool to be sent to Erica in follow-up"}, {"name": "Notion", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Used for separate pages and clean mappings for JD variants"}, {"name": "Erica debrief", "type": "EVENT", "context": "Meeting summarizing Erica's background, layoff context, and commitments"}, {"name": "RevOps role closed", "type": "EVENT", "context": "Decision to mark RevOps role as closed"}], "relationships": [{"from": "V", "to": "Logan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Encouraging Logan to take 10 days offline from Careerspan"}, {"from": "Logan", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Team member taking break due to exhaustion"}, {"from": "Erica", "to": "Google", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Former DevRel employee, recently laid off"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Erica", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Committed to follow-up email, tools, and full Careerspan account"}, {"from": "Transcend", "to": "Next Play", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Both communities used for distribution in edtech context"}, {"from": "Davide", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Multiple roles being clarified and tested"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "JD A/B testing", "type": "USES", "context": "Maintaining separate Notion pages for each JD variant"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Notion", "type": "USES", "context": "Clean mappings for JD variants"}, {"from": "Davis", "to": "TeamWork Online", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "High-potential prospect call"}, {"from": "Rahul", "to": "Zeni", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Coordinating 1099 processing"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Zeni", "type": "USES", "context": "Back-office 1099 compliance handling"}]}