{"entities": [{"name": "Theresa", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact at Remotely Good, works on Social Impact SF community"}, {"name": "Logan", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Works at Careerspan, handling operational follow-up with Theresa"}, {"name": "Vrijen", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Meeting with Amanda from MLH on Wednesday"}, {"name": "Amanda", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact at Major League Hacking (MLH)"}, {"name": "Gary", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Person V went to get during handoff"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company, partnering with Remotely Good on pilot"}, {"name": "Remotely Good", "type": "ORG", "context": "Theresa's organization, receiving 100+ license codes"}, {"name": "Social Impact SF", "type": "ORG", "context": "Micro-community Theresa runs, focus on values and careers intersection"}, {"name": "Major League Hacking", "type": "ORG", "context": "MLH - Amanda's organization, relevant for hackathon planning"}, {"name": "Tech Week Oct 7", "type": "EVENT", "context": "Event Theresa is involved with, pilot sync scheduled after"}, {"name": "November diversity/equity hackathon", "type": "EVENT", "context": "Event Theresa is planning, MLH connection to help accelerate"}, {"name": "Wednesday MLH meeting", "type": "EVENT", "context": "Vrijen chatting with Amanda about hackathon context"}, {"name": "Pilot Kickoff", "type": "EVENT", "context": "30-minute sync planned for next week with Theresa"}, {"name": "Micro-community recruiting", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Described as the real frontier in recruiting - capturing people where values and careers intersect"}, {"name": "License Codes", "type": "TOOL", "context": "100+ Remotely Good codes on custom branded page for community distribution"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Theresa", "to": "Remotely Good", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Theresa's email domain is remotelygood.com"}, {"from": "Theresa", "to": "Social Impact SF", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Theresa's work on Social Impact SF community"}, {"from": "Logan", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Logan's email domain is careerspan.com"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Amanda", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Chatting Wednesday about MLH connection"}, {"from": "Amanda", "to": "Major League Hacking", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Amanda is from MLH"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Remotely Good", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Partnership on community pilot with license codes"}, {"from": "Major League Hacking", "to": "November diversity/equity hackathon", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "MLH connection to help accelerate hackathon planning"}, {"from": "Social Impact SF", "to": "Micro-community recruiting", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Example of micro-community where values and careers intersect"}, {"from": "Logan", "to": "Theresa", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Logan handling activation guide and pilot calendar sync"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Micro-community recruiting", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Careerspan views micro-communities as the real frontier in recruiting"}]}