{"entities": [{"name": "V", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder of Careerspan, strategizing partnerships and community leverage"}, {"name": "Logan", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Team member creating TikTok content, received interest from Teal CEO"}, {"name": "Ilya", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Team member who reacted to Logan's Teal news"}, {"name": "Teal CEO", "type": "PERSON", "context": "CEO of Teal who discovered Logan's TikTok and scheduled a call"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company providing candidate intake links and data collection"}, {"name": "Superposition", "type": "ORG", "context": "Partner company handling recruiting operations and candidate engagement"}, {"name": "Teal", "type": "ORG", "context": "Major career-tech platform with approximately 2 million job seekers"}, {"name": "McKinsey alumni", "type": "ORG", "context": "High-signal founder community V is part of"}, {"name": "Front door strategy", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Careerspan serves as entry point for founders, feeding candidates to Superposition"}, {"name": "Revenue sharing model", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Careerspan receives cut for Superposition client intros plus recurring fees"}, {"name": "Careerspan link", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Technology for candidate intake and data collection"}, {"name": "TikTok", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Platform where Logan creates content that attracted Teal CEO"}, {"name": "Job board", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Cleaned up board reflecting open roles, nearly production-ready"}, {"name": "Teal CEO call", "type": "EVENT", "context": "One-hour call scheduled for following week after LinkedIn connection"}], "relationships": [{"from": "V", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "V is founder of Careerspan"}, {"from": "Logan", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Logan is a team member"}, {"from": "Ilya", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Ilya is a team member"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Superposition", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Partnership where Careerspan is front door feeding clients to Superposition"}, {"from": "V", "to": "McKinsey alumni", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "V has presence in this founder community"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Front door strategy", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "V proposed this partnership structure"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Revenue sharing model", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "V outlined this compensation structure"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Careerspan link", "type": "USES", "context": "Core technology for candidate intake"}, {"from": "Logan", "to": "TikTok", "type": "USES", "context": "Logan creates content on TikTok"}, {"from": "Teal CEO", "to": "Teal", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "CEO leads the career-tech platform"}, {"from": "Teal CEO", "to": "Logan", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "CEO discovered Logan via TikTok and connected on LinkedIn"}]}