{"entities": [{"name": "Daniel", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder actively raising capital, seeking intros into infra funds"}, {"name": "Lance", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder actively raising capital, seeking intros into rehabs"}, {"name": "Abby", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder actively raising capital"}, {"name": "Felix", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder actively raising capital"}, {"name": "Tomas", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder seeking intros into O&G operators"}, {"name": "V", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Peer in network benefiting from vertical EIR path for investor/customer access"}, {"name": "J.P. Morgan", "type": "ORG", "context": "Sponsorship interest in the network, upgrades perceived quality"}, {"name": "McKinsey", "type": "ORG", "context": "Partnerships with NY, SF, London offices"}, {"name": "GiveWell", "type": "ORG", "context": "Session planned as reputational play for structured giving"}, {"name": "Vertical EIRs", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Formalized path for tailored investor and customer access"}, {"name": "Relationship-driven sales", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "GTM approach dependent on network intros for health systems, O&G, infra funds, sports leagues"}, {"name": "GiveWell session", "type": "EVENT", "context": "Reputational play aligning founder group with thoughtful, structured giving"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Daniel", "to": "Vertical EIRs", "type": "USES", "context": "Using forum as curated investor-discovery surface while raising"}, {"from": "Lance", "to": "Vertical EIRs", "type": "USES", "context": "Using forum for investor discovery and rehab sector intros"}, {"from": "Abby", "to": "Vertical EIRs", "type": "USES", "context": "Using forum as investor-discovery surface while raising"}, {"from": "Felix", "to": "Vertical EIRs", "type": "USES", "context": "Using forum as investor-discovery surface while raising"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Vertical EIRs", "type": "USES", "context": "Formalized path for tailored investor and customer access"}, {"from": "Tomas", "to": "Relationship-driven sales", "type": "USES", "context": "Seeking intros into O&G operators through network"}, {"from": "J.P. Morgan", "to": "Vertical EIRs", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Sponsorship interest upgrades network credibility with investors and enterprise buyers"}, {"from": "McKinsey", "to": "Vertical EIRs", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Partnerships with NY, SF, London offices enhance network quality"}, {"from": "GiveWell session", "to": "Vertical EIRs", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Aligns founder group with structured giving for reputational benefit"}]}