{"entities": [{"name": "David", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Collaborator involved in financial planning, SHRM outreach, and Jim Conti relationship"}, {"name": "Logan", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact for contract language clarification regarding cash flow predictability"}, {"name": "Jim Conti", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Potential soft intro target for Careerspan/hiring space conversation"}, {"name": "Ben", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact at Zo who offered standing calls with Vrijen"}, {"name": "Vrijen", "type": "PERSON", "context": "The user (V), involved in multiple resolution paths and advisor positioning"}, {"name": "SHRM", "type": "ORG", "context": "Target organization for intro; exact contact and decision authority needed"}, {"name": "Zo", "type": "ORG", "context": "Company where Vrijen has advisor relationship; planning weekly standing calls"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company; topic for potential conversation with Jim Conti about hiring space"}, {"name": "LinkedIn", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Used by David for searching SHRM target contact"}], "relationships": [{"from": "David", "to": "Logan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "David getting contract language info via Logan"}, {"from": "David", "to": "Jim Conti", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "David owns the relationship and will gauge receptivity"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "David", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Collaborating on outstanding questions and resolution paths"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Logan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Vrijen to ask Logan about contract language"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Zo", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Advisor commitment level and positioning in org"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Ben", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Contact at Zo for clarifying standing meeting cadence"}, {"from": "David", "to": "LinkedIn", "type": "USES", "context": "For searching SHRM target contact"}, {"from": "Jim Conti", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Potential conversation topic about hiring space"}, {"from": "David", "to": "SHRM", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Responsible for finding exact target contact"}]}