{"entities": [{"name": "V (Vrijen)", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder trying to protect team from burnout while managing rich pipeline; seeking external validation and relief"}, {"name": "Logan", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Team member handling community/posting tasks, at risk of burnout, being encouraged to take offline break"}, {"name": "Ilsa", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Team member providing quiet operational support with Notion and JD problems"}, {"name": "Davis", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact associated with TeamWork Online meeting"}, {"name": "Erica", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Prospect in the pipeline"}, {"name": "Davide", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Prospect with messy JDs creating extra cognitive load"}, {"name": "Bradford", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Prospect deprioritized by the team"}, {"name": "Arsène Wenger", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Famous football manager mentioned in V's fantasy of success"}, {"name": "TeamWork Online", "type": "ORG", "context": "Company with upcoming meeting that V hopes will provide financial relief and recognition"}, {"name": "Darwinbox", "type": "ORG", "context": "Prospect company in the pipeline"}, {"name": "Marvin", "type": "ORG", "context": "Prospect company in the pipeline"}, {"name": "Transcend", "type": "ORG", "context": "Prospect company in the pipeline"}, {"name": "Next Play", "type": "ORG", "context": "Prospect company in the pipeline"}, {"name": "Mutual care and protection", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Team dynamic where V protects Logan from burnout, Logan protects company by continuing work"}, {"name": "Need for external validation", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "V's desire for someone to recognize the work done and provide relief"}, {"name": "Tension between ambition and capacity", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Core challenge: rich pipeline vs constrained emotional and cognitive bandwidth"}, {"name": "Emotional and cognitive bandwidth", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Constraint limiting team's ability to pursue all opportunities"}, {"name": "Notion", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Tool where messy problems arise that Ilsa helps resolve"}, {"name": "Davis/TeamWork Online meeting", "type": "EVENT", "context": "Upcoming meeting V hopes will bring financial relief and emotional recognition"}], "relationships": [{"from": "V (Vrijen)", "to": "Logan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "V actively protecting Logan from burnout, encouraging offline break"}, {"from": "V (Vrijen)", "to": "Ilsa", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Ilsa provides operational support to V's team"}, {"from": "Logan", "to": "V (Vrijen)", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Continuing community/posting tasks while naming limits"}, {"from": "Ilsa", "to": "Notion", "type": "USES", "context": "Jumps into messy Notion and JD problems"}, {"from": "V (Vrijen)", "to": "Davis", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Has upcoming meeting with Davis at TeamWork Online"}, {"from": "Davis", "to": "TeamWork Online", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Associated with TeamWork Online meeting"}, {"from": "V (Vrijen)", "to": "Need for external validation", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Wants someone to recognize work done and provide relief"}, {"from": "V (Vrijen)", "to": "Mutual care and protection", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Core dynamic in how V relates to team"}, {"from": "V (Vrijen)", "to": "Tension between ambition and capacity", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Recognizes constraint between rich pipeline and limited bandwidth"}, {"from": "V (Vrijen)", "to": "Erica", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Prospect in pipeline"}, {"from": "V (Vrijen)", "to": "Davide", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Prospect whose messy JDs create cognitive load"}, {"from": "V (Vrijen)", "to": "Darwinbox", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Prospect company in pipeline"}, {"from": "V (Vrijen)", "to": "Marvin", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Prospect company in pipeline"}, {"from": "V (Vrijen)", "to": "Transcend", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Prospect company in pipeline"}, {"from": "V (Vrijen)", "to": "Next Play", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Prospect company in pipeline"}, {"from": "V (Vrijen)", "to": "Bradford", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Prospect deprioritized due to bandwidth constraints"}]}