{"entities": [{"name": "Michael", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Evaluator at Johnson, leading assessment of Careerspan as potential resume tool"}, {"name": "Vrijen", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder of Careerspan, presenting to Johnson for potential partnership"}, {"name": "Diane", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact at Columbia SPS, reference for Careerspan institutional use"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company, being evaluated as resume tooling replacement/complement"}, {"name": "Columbia SPS", "type": "ORG", "context": "Columbia School of Professional Studies, existing Careerspan institutional user"}, {"name": "UMass Eisenberg", "type": "ORG", "context": "University with Careerspan proof-points and survey results"}, {"name": "Aspire", "type": "ORG", "context": "Organization with Careerspan proof-point summaries"}, {"name": "Johnson", "type": "ORG", "context": "Business school evaluating Careerspan for student resume support"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Michael", "to": "Johnson", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Leading Careerspan evaluation for Johnson"}, {"from": "Michael", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Evaluating as first in series of tools to assess"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Diane", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Will connect Johnson to Diane as reference"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "UMass Eisenberg", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Has leaders as references and survey data"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Aspire", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Has proof-point summaries to share"}, {"from": "Diane", "to": "Columbia SPS", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Institutional contact for Careerspan reference"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Johnson", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Candidate to replace/complement current resume tooling"}]}