{"entities": [{"name": "Tomas", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder positioning for O&G intros, treats calls as sales surface"}, {"name": "Lance", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder positioning for rehabs intros, treats calls as sales surface"}, {"name": "Daniel", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder positioning for infra fund intros, treats calls as sales surface"}, {"name": "Vrijen Attawar", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Repeat participant, relationship node, hiring expertise, Careerspan founder"}, {"name": "J.P. Morgan", "type": "ORG", "context": "Sponsorship interest in network, upgrading perceived quality for investors"}, {"name": "McKinsey", "type": "ORG", "context": "Partnerships with NY, SF, London offices for network credibility"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company, mentioned in business angle context"}, {"name": "GiveWell", "type": "ORG", "context": "Session partner, reputational play for structured giving alignment"}, {"name": "Relationship-driven sales", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Business model for health systems, O&G operators, infra funds, sports leagues"}, {"name": "Sales surface", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "How founders treat calls—as sales opportunities not just social time"}, {"name": "Brand & Credibility", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Network quality perception upgrade via sponsorships and partnerships"}, {"name": "Reputational play", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Aligning founder group with thoughtful structured giving vs extraction"}, {"name": "New York events", "type": "EVENT", "context": "Where V participates as repeat attendee and relationship node"}, {"name": "GiveWell session", "type": "EVENT", "context": "Reputational play aligning founders with structured philanthropy"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Tomas", "to": "Relationship-driven sales", "type": "USES", "context": "Positions for O&G intros as sales strategy"}, {"from": "Lance", "to": "Relationship-driven sales", "type": "USES", "context": "Positions for rehabs intros as sales strategy"}, {"from": "Daniel", "to": "Relationship-driven sales", "type": "USES", "context": "Positions for infra fund intros as sales strategy"}, {"from": "J.P. Morgan", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Sponsorship interest raises network credibility"}, {"from": "McKinsey", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Partnerships upgrade perceived network quality"}, {"from": "Vrijen Attawar", "to": "New York events", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Repeat participant and relationship node at these events"}, {"from": "Vrijen Attawar", "to": "Relationship-driven sales", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Hiring expertise positions him as network resource for relationship-driven businesses"}, {"from": "GiveWell session", "to": "Brand & Credibility", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Reputational play aligning with thoughtful giving rather than extraction"}]}