{"entities": [{"name": "V", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Owner of multiple deliverables including Sapphire materials, investor proposal, UMass follow-up, Emory follow-up, and Daniel outreach"}, {"name": "Logan", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Collaborator working with V on VC narrative, FOMO strategy, and Emory campus rollout discussions; owns Irene outreach"}, {"name": "V's father", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Potential investor being presented with loan-first capital structure proposal"}, {"name": "Nicole", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact at Emory who previously requested materials; gateway to campus-wide rollout"}, {"name": "Irene", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Early-talent scout visiting multiple campuses for Soma; potential channel for pre-visit student identification"}, {"name": "Daniel", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Runs a job-fair company; potential integration partner for employer-student triage"}, {"name": "Sapphire", "type": "ORG", "context": "VC firm; source of call notes informing investor narrative and FOMO strategy"}, {"name": "UMass", "type": "ORG", "context": "University where pilot was conducted; target for paid engagement follow-up"}, {"name": "Emory", "type": "ORG", "context": "University where Nicole works; target for campus-wide rollout"}, {"name": "Soma", "type": "ORG", "context": "Company Irene scouts for; visits multiple campuses"}, {"name": "VC narrative", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Investor-facing story being refined based on Sapphire call insights"}, {"name": "FOMO strategy", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Approach being developed alongside VC narrative to create investor urgency"}, {"name": "loan-first structure", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Proposed capital structure where remaining tranches come as loans with repayment waterfall"}, {"name": "early-talent scouting", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Pre-visit identification of high-signal students at campuses"}, {"name": "Sapphire call", "type": "EVENT", "context": "VC conversation generating notes and insights for investor strategy"}, {"name": "UMass pilot", "type": "EVENT", "context": "Completed pilot whose results support follow-up proposal for paid engagement"}], "relationships": [{"from": "V", "to": "Logan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Collaborating on VC narrative, FOMO strategy, and Emory rollout discussions"}, {"from": "V", "to": "V's father", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Preparing investment proposal for family capital"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Nicole", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Contact at Emory for campus rollout discussions"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Daniel", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Potential partner for job-fair integration"}, {"from": "Logan", "to": "Irene", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Will reach out about early-talent scouting opportunity"}, {"from": "Irene", "to": "Soma", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Visits campuses on behalf of Soma for talent scouting"}, {"from": "Daniel", "to": "job-fair company", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Runs the job-fair company"}, {"from": "Nicole", "to": "Emory", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "V's contact at the university"}, {"from": "V", "to": "loan-first structure", "type": "USES", "context": "Proposing this capital structure to father"}, {"from": "V", "to": "VC narrative", "type": "USES", "context": "Developing investor-facing story from Sapphire insights"}, {"from": "V", "to": "FOMO strategy", "type": "USES", "context": "Developing urgency approach for investors"}, {"from": "Sapphire call", "to": "VC narrative", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Call insights inform the narrative development"}, {"from": "UMass pilot", "to": "UMass", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Pilot conducted at UMass supports follow-up proposal"}]}