{"entities": [{"name": "Anthony", "type": "PERSON", "context": "User who tried multiple career tech tools over past 2-3 months, values agency over automation"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "Career tech tool Anthony tried 3+ months ago, liked voice capture feature but abandoned"}, {"name": "Obsidian", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Identified as the real competition for Careerspan"}, {"name": "LazyApply", "type": "ORG", "context": "Auto-apply tool, likely candidate Anthony may have tried"}, {"name": "Sonara", "type": "ORG", "context": "Auto-apply tool, likely candidate Anthony may have tried"}, {"name": "Massive", "type": "ORG", "context": "Auto-apply tool, likely candidate Anthony may have tried"}, {"name": "Loxo", "type": "ORG", "context": "Outreach automation tool, likely candidate Anthony may have tried"}, {"name": "Gem", "type": "ORG", "context": "Outreach automation tool, likely candidate Anthony may have tried"}, {"name": "Aura", "type": "ORG", "context": "Outreach automation tool, likely candidate Anthony may have tried"}, {"name": "Huntr", "type": "ORG", "context": "Job organization tool, likely candidate Anthony may have tried"}, {"name": "Teal", "type": "ORG", "context": "Job organization tool, likely candidate Anthony may have tried"}, {"name": "JobTracker", "type": "ORG", "context": "Job organization tool, likely candidate Anthony may have tried"}, {"name": "Careerflow", "type": "ORG", "context": "Resume optimization tool, likely candidate Anthony may have tried"}, {"name": "Resume Worded", "type": "ORG", "context": "Resume optimization tool, likely candidate Anthony may have tried"}, {"name": "Voice Capture", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Feature Anthony found genuinely differentiating in career tools"}, {"name": "Agency Over Automation", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Anthony's core value - prefers control over automated solutions"}, {"name": "Auto-Apply Tools", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Category of tools Anthony dismissed as solving non-problems"}, {"name": "Cold DM Automation", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Category of tools Anthony rejected, prefers manual research"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Anthony", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "USES", "context": "Tried 3+ months ago, liked voice capture but abandoned"}, {"from": "Anthony", "to": "Auto-Apply Tools", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Dismissed as solving non-problems"}, {"from": "Anthony", "to": "Cold DM Automation", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Rejected, prefers doing own research"}, {"from": "Anthony", "to": "Agency Over Automation", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Core value driving tool adoption decisions"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Voice Capture", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Key differentiating feature Anthony appreciated"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Obsidian", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Identified as real competitive threat"}, {"from": "LazyApply", "to": "Auto-Apply Tools", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Example of auto-apply category"}, {"from": "Sonara", "to": "Auto-Apply Tools", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Example of auto-apply category"}, {"from": "Massive", "to": "Auto-Apply Tools", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Example of auto-apply category"}, {"from": "Huntr", "to": "Teal", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Both in job organization tool category"}, {"from": "Loxo", "to": "Cold DM Automation", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Example of outreach automation category"}]}