{"entities": [{"name": "V (Vrijen)", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder of Careerspan, navigating acquisition interest and fundraising"}, {"name": "Logan", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Key team member at Careerspan; V wants to do right by Logan in any acquisition outcome"}, {"name": "Ilsa", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Key team member or stakeholder at Careerspan; V wants to do right by Ilsa"}, {"name": "Jaya", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Conversation partner who asks V about acquisition processes for small startups"}, {"name": "Sarah", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Friend of V who has a relevant acquisition case study"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company, receiving inbound acquisition interest from multiple parties"}, {"name": "Teal", "type": "ORG", "context": "Potential acquirer expressing interest in Careerspan"}, {"name": "HireVue", "type": "ORG", "context": "Former CEO is leading a new company that has expressed acquisition interest in Careerspan"}, {"name": "TeamWork Online", "type": "ORG", "context": "Sports-focused ATS that has expressed acquisition interest in Careerspan"}, {"name": "HireVue Former CEO's New Company", "type": "ORG", "context": "New company led by the former CEO of HireVue, one of the potential acquirers"}, {"name": "Honorable Exit", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "V's belief that acquisition outcomes should leave key people with a good experience, even if investors lose money"}, {"name": "Ego-Free Leadership", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "V explicitly states he has no ego about retaining the CEO title and would support a transition"}, {"name": "Acquisition Over Fundraising", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "V's observation that serious acquisition interest has exceeded investor interest during the fundraising period"}], "relationships": [{"from": "V (Vrijen)", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Founder and current CEO of Careerspan"}, {"from": "V (Vrijen)", "to": "Logan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "V frames doing right by Logan as a primary goal in any acquisition outcome"}, {"from": "V (Vrijen)", "to": "Ilsa", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "V frames doing right by Ilsa as a primary goal in any acquisition outcome"}, {"from": "V (Vrijen)", "to": "Jaya", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Jaya engages V in conversation about acquisition strategy"}, {"from": "V (Vrijen)", "to": "Sarah", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "V describes Sarah as a friend and references her acquisition case study"}, {"from": "Teal", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Teal is a potential acquirer of Careerspan"}, {"from": "HireVue Former CEO's New Company", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "New company led by former HireVue CEO has expressed acquisition interest"}, {"from": "TeamWork Online", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Sports-focused ATS expressing acquisition interest in Careerspan"}, {"from": "V (Vrijen)", "to": "Honorable Exit", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "V wants an outcome that feels honorable and leaves key people with a good experience"}, {"from": "V (Vrijen)", "to": "Ego-Free Leadership", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "V has no ego about retaining CEO title; willing to step back if acquirer prefers Logan"}, {"from": "V (Vrijen)", "to": "Acquisition Over Fundraising", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "V notes more serious acquisition interest recently than investor interest across entire fundraising period"}]}