{"entities": [{"name": "V", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Vrijen, founder of Careerspan, sharing strategically sensitive information with trusted contacts"}, {"name": "Jaya", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Known by V for ~18 months, trusted contact, associated with Bonfire, evaluating Careerspan adoption"}, {"name": "Logan", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Stakeholder in Careerspan that V wants to do right by"}, {"name": "Ilsa", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Stakeholder in Careerspan that V wants to do right by"}, {"name": "advisors", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Stakeholders in Careerspan that V feels responsibility toward"}, {"name": "investors", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Stakeholders in Careerspan that V wants to honor in the outcome"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company, framed as legacy and bridge not just business"}, {"name": "Bonfire", "type": "ORG", "context": "Jaya's company, thoughtful customer evaluating hiring tools"}, {"name": "power symmetry", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Relationship dynamic where neither side is supplicant, mutual exploration"}, {"name": "shared mindset on tools", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Common perspective between V and Jaya on evaluating hiring tools"}], "relationships": [{"from": "V", "to": "Jaya", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Known for ~18 months, comfortable sharing sensitive strategic information"}, {"from": "Jaya", "to": "Bonfire", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Jaya is associated with Bonfire as decision-maker"}, {"from": "Jaya", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "USES", "context": "Considering adoption partly as bet on V, not just product"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Frames as legacy and bridge, wants to land the plane honorably"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Logan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Feels responsibility to do right by as part of legacy"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Ilsa", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Feels responsibility to do right by as part of legacy"}, {"from": "V", "to": "advisors", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Feels responsibility to honor their investment and support"}, {"from": "V", "to": "investors", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Trying to land the plane honorably for all stakeholders"}, {"from": "Bonfire", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Potential customer relationship, evaluating for hiring process improvement"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Jaya", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Power symmetry - mutual exploration with meaningful gains for both"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Jaya", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Shared mindset on tools - both value genuine improvement over hype"}]}