{"entities": [{"name": "Davit", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Individual providing deliverables; seeking roles at Deep Tune, True Meter, and Zo Computer"}, {"name": "V", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Vrijen; receiving deliverables, forwarding to contacts, and advocating for Davit"}, {"name": "Holly", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact at Deep Tune; receiving Davit's resume via V"}, {"name": "Ali", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact at True Meter; potential recipient of Davit's materials"}, {"name": "Deep Tune", "type": "ORG", "context": "Company with open role; Holly is the contact"}, {"name": "True Meter", "type": "ORG", "context": "Company with AI-native backend roles; Ali is the contact"}, {"name": "Zo Computer", "type": "ORG", "context": "Company with infrastructure role opportunity"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company; provides story library, profiles, and strategic positioning analyses"}, {"name": "Warmer Jobs", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Job discovery platform; optional for Davit to use with LinkedIn graph upload"}, {"name": "STAR-style stories", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Framework for structuring professional stories covering full-stack, AI research, and agentic tooling work"}, {"name": "Strategic positioning", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Careerspan output format for role-specific analyses"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Davit", "to": "V", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Davit providing deliverables to V for job search advocacy"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Holly", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "V forwarding Davit's resume to Holly at Deep Tune"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Ali", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "V planning to forward materials to Ali at True Meter"}, {"from": "Holly", "to": "Deep Tune", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Holly is V's contact at Deep Tune"}, {"from": "Ali", "to": "True Meter", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Ali is V's contact at True Meter"}, {"from": "Davit", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "USES", "context": "Davit storing stories and generating role-specific analyses via Careerspan"}, {"from": "Davit", "to": "Warmer Jobs", "type": "USES", "context": "Optional use for additional job leads and LinkedIn graph analysis"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Strategic positioning", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Careerspan generates strategic positioning outputs for target roles"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Davit", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "V using Careerspan outputs to inform advocacy emails for Davit"}]}