{"entities": [{"name": "Daniel", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder of Veridu AI, raising ~$2M pre-seed for due-diligence automation"}, {"name": "Veridu AI", "type": "ORG", "context": "Due-diligence automation platform for legal, technical, and financial due diligence for infrastructure investors"}, {"name": "Energy infrastructure", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Primary focus area for Veridu AI's due-diligence automation"}, {"name": "Energy Impact Partners", "type": "ORG", "context": "Fund suggested by Ulrik for Daniel to engage ahead of Series A"}, {"name": "Lance", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder of Livelihood, recently completed Antler's Dispatch program, assembling pre-seed"}, {"name": "Livelihood", "type": "ORG", "context": "Addiction recovery platform for elite professionals combining coaching and GLP-1 medications"}, {"name": "GLP-1 medications", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Medications used by Livelihood for cravings reduction and long-term recovery"}, {"name": "Antler", "type": "ORG", "context": "Venture program operator running the Dispatch program"}, {"name": "Dispatch program", "type": "EVENT", "context": "Antler's late-stage program in NYC that Lance recently completed"}, {"name": "Junaid", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Founder of fentanyl testing-strip company, strategic peer for Lance"}, {"name": "Ulrik", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Connector/advisor introducing Daniel to Energy Impact Partners and Lance to Junaid"}, {"name": "Vrijen", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Owner of this knowledge system (V)"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Daniel", "to": "Veridu AI", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Daniel is founder of Veridu AI"}, {"from": "Daniel", "to": "Ulrik", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Connected through network, Ulrik advising on investor strategy"}, {"from": "Ulrik", "to": "Daniel", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Suggests engaging Energy Impact Partners ahead of Series A"}, {"from": "Veridu AI", "to": "Energy infrastructure", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Company's focus area for due-diligence automation"}, {"from": "Lance", "to": "Livelihood", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Lance is founder of Livelihood"}, {"from": "Livelihood", "to": "GLP-1 medications", "type": "USES", "context": "Platform incorporates GLP-1 medications for cravings reduction"}, {"from": "Lance", "to": "Dispatch program", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Recently completed Antler's late-stage Dispatch program in NYC"}, {"from": "Lance", "to": "Ulrik", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Connected through network"}, {"from": "Ulrik", "to": "Lance", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Committing to introduce Lance to Junaid as strategic peer"}, {"from": "Ulrik", "to": "Junaid", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Connected enough to make introductions"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Daniel", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Tracked in V's knowledge system"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Lance", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Tracked in V's knowledge system"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Ulrik", "type": "KNOWS", "context": "Tracked in V's knowledge system as connector"}]}