{"entities": [{"name": "Logan", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Collaborator managing university outreach calls and follow-ups for Careerspan"}, {"name": "Lauren", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact on the UMass call"}, {"name": "Melissa", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Head of career services at UMass"}, {"name": "Andy Chan", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact at Wake Forest university"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company being pitched to universities and alumni networks"}, {"name": "Emory", "type": "ORG", "context": "University in active pilot with Careerspan, current students already in motion"}, {"name": "UMass", "type": "ORG", "context": "University with upcoming call scheduled at 10:30"}, {"name": "Wake Forest", "type": "ORG", "context": "University targeted for follow-up outreach"}, {"name": "Wharton", "type": "ORG", "context": "University targeted for follow-up outreach"}, {"name": "HBS", "type": "ORG", "context": "Harvard Business School, targeted for follow-up outreach"}, {"name": "Tuck", "type": "ORG", "context": "Dartmouth Tuck, targeted for follow-up outreach"}, {"name": "Cornell", "type": "ORG", "context": "University that requested five accounts; Logan has done Loom demos"}, {"name": "Quinicia", "type": "ORG", "context": "Competitor or tool in the landscape being evaluated against Careerspan"}, {"name": "Alumni Employer Phase", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Phase 2 strategy where Emory proposes Careerspan to alumni who want to hire"}, {"name": "Free Onboarding During Pilot", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Strategy to avoid line-item pricing by offering free onboarding and support to alumni employers during pilot window"}, {"name": "Minimizing Friction and Direct Pricing", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Principle to accelerate higher-ed adoption given slow movement and budget constraints"}, {"name": "Loom", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Video demo tool Logan used to demo Careerspan to Cornell contacts"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Logan", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Manages university outreach and partnership pipeline"}, {"from": "Logan", "to": "UMass", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Leading upcoming call with Lauren and Melissa"}, {"from": "Logan", "to": "Cornell", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Has done Loom demos, needs to follow up on five account requests"}, {"from": "Melissa", "to": "UMass", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Head of career services at UMass"}, {"from": "Lauren", "to": "UMass", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Participating in UMass call"}, {"from": "Andy Chan", "to": "Wake Forest", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "University contact for Careerspan outreach"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Emory", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Active Phase 1 pilot with current students, Phase 2 alumni employer expansion planned"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "UMass", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Upcoming partnership call scheduled"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Wake Forest", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Planned follow-up using learnings from UMass and Emory"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Wharton", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Planned follow-up outreach"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "HBS", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Planned follow-up outreach"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Tuck", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Planned follow-up outreach"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Cornell", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Cornell requested five accounts, demos completed"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Quinicia", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Competitor in the tool landscape being assessed"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Free Onboarding During Pilot", "type": "USES", "context": "Strategic pricing approach to reduce friction for university adoption"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Minimizing Friction and Direct Pricing", "type": "USES", "context": "Core adoption acceleration principle for budget-constrained higher-ed partners"}, {"from": "Alumni Employer Phase", "to": "Emory", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Phase 2 plan where Emory proposes Careerspan to alumni employers"}, {"from": "Logan", "to": "Loom", "type": "USES", "context": "Used Loom for demo videos sent to Cornell contacts"}]}