{"entities": [{"name": "V", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Main subject, handling client calls and prioritization decisions"}, {"name": "Logan", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Collaborator who reviews client conversations with V and provides strategic input"}, {"name": "Davis", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Client contact at TeamWork Online with scheduled call"}, {"name": "TeamWork Online", "type": "ORG", "context": "Client company with potentially transformative deal opportunity"}, {"name": "Darwinbox", "type": "ORG", "context": "Prospect with call scheduled later in the week"}, {"name": "Bradford", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact at a company being evaluated for deprioritization"}, {"name": "Teal", "type": "ORG", "context": "Alternative prospect with better brand and product value potential"}, {"name": "FutureFit", "type": "ORG", "context": "Alternative prospect in open-source talent ecosystems space"}, {"name": "ruthless prioritization", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Shared principle of focusing on partners that bring revenue, brand leverage, or both given limited energy and runway"}], "relationships": [{"from": "V", "to": "Logan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Review client and prospect conversations together, share strategic decisions"}, {"from": "V", "to": "TeamWork Online", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Scheduled call with potential for transformative financial and emotional outcome"}, {"from": "V", "to": "Darwinbox", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "V handling meeting while Logan is traveling"}, {"from": "Logan", "to": "Bradford", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Recommends deprioritizing due to budget concerns and lack of strategic upside"}, {"from": "Teal", "to": "Bradford", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Positioned as better alternative option"}, {"from": "FutureFit", "to": "Bradford", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Positioned as better alternative option"}, {"from": "V", "to": "ruthless prioritization", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Shared principle driving partner selection decisions"}, {"from": "Logan", "to": "ruthless prioritization", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Shared principle driving partner selection decisions"}]}