{"entities": [{"name": "Michael Maher", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Frames the meeting; leading Johnson's reassessment of career resources"}, {"name": "Amanda Moser", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Participant in the Johnson meeting"}, {"name": "Victoria Preble", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Participant in the Johnson meeting"}, {"name": "Chase Hudson", "type": "PERSON", "context": "From Johnson Career Management Center"}, {"name": "Vrijen", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Johnson MBA '22, founder presenting Careerspan, background in college admissions and career coaching"}, {"name": "Donna", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Simulated product manager persona used in Careerspan demo"}, {"name": "Johnson Career Management Center", "type": "ORG", "context": "Cornell Johnson's career office reassessing their toolbox of resources"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company; first resource being evaluated in Johnson's review cycle"}, {"name": "Johnson", "type": "ORG", "context": "Cornell Johnson Graduate School of Management"}, {"name": "Self-understanding", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "V's framing of unmet need sitting one layer below mechanical resume generation"}, {"name": "STAR format", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Interview answer structure produced by Careerspan AI"}, {"name": "Vibe check", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Careerspan feature showing alignment between candidate stories and job descriptions"}, {"name": "AI coach", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Careerspan's adaptive questioning system that asks follow-up questions rather than fixed scripts"}, {"name": "Voice recording feature", "type": "TOOL", "context": "Click-to-record rambling that AI cleans up and structures into stories"}, {"name": "B01 Meeting", "type": "EVENT", "context": "First evaluation meeting between Johnson Career Management Center and Careerspan"}], "relationships": [{"from": "Michael Maher", "to": "Johnson Career Management Center", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Leading the resource evaluation process"}, {"from": "Chase Hudson", "to": "Johnson Career Management Center", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Staff member participating in evaluation"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "Founder presenting the product"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Johnson", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "MBA Class of 2022 alumnus"}, {"from": "Vrijen", "to": "Self-understanding", "type": "BELIEVES", "context": "Frames this as the core unmet need below resume mechanics"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "AI coach", "type": "USES", "context": "Core feature for adaptive candidate conversations"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Vibe check", "type": "USES", "context": "Feature for job-candidate alignment analysis"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "STAR format", "type": "USES", "context": "Output format for interview answers"}, {"from": "Careerspan", "to": "Voice recording feature", "type": "USES", "context": "Story capture method via spoken rambling"}, {"from": "Johnson Career Management Center", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "First external resource being evaluated in toolbox reassessment"}, {"from": "Johnson Career Management Center", "to": "Johnson", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Career services arm of the business school"}]}