{"entities": [{"name": "David", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Contact operating at intersection of recruiter pipeline and Careerspan, associated with Superposition"}, {"name": "Logan", "type": "PERSON", "context": "Collaborator who performs strategic analysis like acquirer landscape staff ranking"}, {"name": "Superposition", "type": "ORG", "context": "Company where David may be acting as recruiter-of-record, potential employer client"}, {"name": "Careerspan", "type": "ORG", "context": "V's company, platform that could be used to avoid recruiter commissions"}, {"name": "FutureFit AI", "type": "ORG", "context": "Potential acquirer, categorized on cheapskates end with limited cash potential"}, {"name": "ETS", "type": "ORG", "context": "Potential acquirer, categorized on cheapskates end with limited cash potential"}, {"name": "Teal", "type": "ORG", "context": "Potential acquirer, categorized on cheapskates end, strategically interesting but low cash"}, {"name": "TeamWork Online", "type": "ORG", "context": "Sports hiring platform, estimated $33M/year revenue, promising acquirer candidate"}, {"name": "HireVue", "type": "ORG", "context": "Company adjacent to a founder who invested ~$10M, potentially capital-constrained"}, {"name": "Claude", "type": "TOOL", "context": "AI used to help re-read and analyze a transcript about potential acquirer"}, {"name": "Commission fairness", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "V's principle of maintaining clear boundaries and appropriate commission structures in client relationships"}, {"name": "Acquirer landscape mapping", "type": "CONCEPT", "context": "Strategic exercise to rank potential buyers by financial firepower and alignment"}], "relationships": [{"from": "David", "to": "Superposition", "type": "WORKS_WITH", "context": "May be acting as recruiter-of-record for Superposition"}, {"from": "David", "to": "Careerspan", "type": "USES", "context": "Potentially using Careerspan to avoid commission while maintaining recruiter pipeline"}, {"from": "Logan", "to": "Acquirer landscape mapping", "type": "USES", "context": "Performed staff ranking analysis of potential acquirers"}, {"from": "FutureFit AI", "to": "Acquirer landscape mapping", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Categorized as cheapskate-tier acquirer"}, {"from": "ETS", "to": "Acquirer landscape mapping", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Categorized as cheapskate-tier acquirer"}, {"from": "Teal", "to": "Acquirer landscape mapping", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Categorized as cheapskate-tier acquirer"}, {"from": "TeamWork Online", "to": "Acquirer landscape mapping", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Promising mid-tier acquirer with revenue capacity"}, {"from": "Claude", "to": "HireVue", "type": "RELATED_TO", "context": "Used to re-analyze transcript revealing capital constraints of HireVue-adjacent founder"}]}